<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>macos on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/macos/</link><description>Recent content in macos on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 11:18:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/macos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Warp, iTerm2, or Alacritty? My Terminal Tinkering Journey</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/10/my_config_and_beautify_solution_of_macos_terminal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 11:18:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/10/my_config_and_beautify_solution_of_macos_terminal/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface As a developer, whether running and debugging code locally or deploying and maintaining projects on remote servers, we can&amp;rsquo;t do without the terminal shown in the image below, which is the black window often seen in sci-fi movies.
Operating systems generally have their default shells, such as &amp;ldquo;Powershell&amp;rdquo; on Windows, and bash or zsh on macOS and Linux systems. Systems with graphical interfaces also come with pre-installed terminal emulators, like &amp;ldquo;Terminal.</description></item><item><title>Automating Window Management: A macOS Window Management System Based on yabai+skhd</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/04/macos_window_management_solution_using_yabai_and_skhd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 13:08:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/04/macos_window_management_solution_using_yabai_and_skhd/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface It has been five years since I started using macOS, beginning with my first MacBook Pro that I saved up for during the summer of 2017. As my work and study needs have grown, I&amp;rsquo;ve gradually begun to use a multi-screen workflow. Because I constantly need to open many windows, such as IDEs, text editing tools, terminals, IM</description></item><item><title>Personal Toolkit (May 2022)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/08/personal_tools_in_2022_may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 15:47:16 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/08/personal_tools_in_2022_may/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a tool enthusiast, firmly believing in the principle &amp;ldquo;to do a good job, one must first sharpen one&amp;rsquo;s tools.&amp;rdquo; I constantly tinker with and optimize my hardware and software, seeking the best solution for each specific need. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve gradually found solutions that best suit my usage habits. Due to work, study, and personal interests, my devices have gone through many iterations.</description></item></channel></rss>