<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>travel on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/travel/</link><description>Recent content in travel on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #57 - Life Elsewhere (Bali Trip)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-04-01 to 2024-04-10.
As I put pen to paper, it&amp;rsquo;s already late May. Unknowingly, two months have slipped by. It&amp;rsquo;s not just the weekly review updates; the multitude of recent events seems to have made it difficult for me to extricate myself from my entire life. But without realizing it myself, this weekly review, a vessel for recording life, has already become a part of me.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #54 - Drifting Plan, Stolen Wallet, and Home Server</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-03-01 to 2024-03-16.
As mentioned in the previous weekly review, I embarked on a drifting plan, which concluded with a nearly two-week journey through &amp;ldquo;Hangzhou -&amp;gt; Shanghai -&amp;gt; Huzhou -&amp;gt; Nanjing -&amp;gt; Beijing&amp;rdquo;. Mostly confined to Jiangsu and Zhejiang, there weren&amp;rsquo;t any extraordinary landscapes; it was more about people and events. Due to my main wallet being stolen without determining the cause, I reinstalled two primary computers, which provided an opportunity to reorganize my development environment configuration.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #39 - First COVID Infection, Past Emotions, and Rediscovered Desire to Share</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from May 1, 2023 to May 20, 2023.
As I type this first line, I realize it has been delayed for three weeks. Many interesting things happened during this period, but it seems my desire to share has been gradually fading. I only jotted down some fragmented thoughts in Logseq, and despite several attempts to organize them, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the right approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #37 - A Fortnight of Leisure (Wuhan | Hong Kong | Mayday)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:39:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from April 3rd to April 18th, 2023.
Perhaps due to my recent change in lifestyle, I had planned numerous engagements as early as March. From the beginning of April, I found myself wandering, experiencing a fortnight of leisure. This journey was akin to a homecoming - departing from Hangzhou where I was raised, to Wuhan, the first place I left home for an extended period, to visit my professor and old friends, and finally to Hong Kong, where I spent some remarkable years, to attend exhibitions and events.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #36 - Gastroenteritis, Nini's Update, and New Journeys</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-25 to 2023-04-02.
Never did I imagine that as a southerner who lived in Hangzhou for over a decade, I would suffer severe adaptation issues upon returning to live in Hangzhou.
In the previous post, I mentioned that Nini was a bit sick due to the bumpy journey and other factors.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #11 - Moods, Travels and Serendipities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 5, 2022 to September 12, 2022.
The past week was quite enriching, both during the workdays and the Mid-Autumn Festival holiday. Work gradually became busier but also more interesting; daily life saw some changes, no longer so dull and mundane; I&amp;rsquo;ve grown accustomed to pulling out my Kindle for a few pages even during short car rides of just a few dozen minutes, quickly becoming immersed; going out has become more frequent, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just aimlessly walking the streets.</description></item></channel></rss>