<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>book on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/book/</link><description>Recent content in book on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #64 - Life Is Here (Stoner and Normal People)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a reflection on life from July 1st to July 9th, 2024.
This week, I maintained an early rising routine for several days, dedicating time to reading and studying with high efficiency. However, establishing a regular pattern still requires time and adjustment. I&amp;rsquo;m also exploring how to enter and switch work modes more swiftly. I&amp;rsquo;m simultaneously reading several books: &amp;ldquo;Atlas Shrugged&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Normal People&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;What My Bones Know&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #16 - Pure Learning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:28:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from October 19 to October 27, 2022.
This week has been busy with work projects, with several consecutive days of overtime, but I&amp;rsquo;ve finally completed my part of the requirements. However, during the spare moments, I managed to go through introductory tutorials for several languages I&amp;rsquo;ve long wanted to learn, which was quite interesting.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #13 - The Joy of Stealing Time from a Busy Schedule</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 23:19:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-19 to 2022-09-26.
This week was unusually busy, with several days where I returned home quite late. Yet, strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s during such times that I seem to find more motivation to do more. I finished a book, caught up on many movies and TV series, and accomplished numerous tasks, both big and small.</description></item></channel></rss>