<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>university on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/university/</link><description>Recent content in university on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:24:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #32 - Wuhan, Long-Awaited Reunions, and Flowing Emotions</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:24:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-21 to 2023-02-26. This week was relatively routine in terms of work, with no particularly urgent tasks. Despite being in a somewhat tense state due to personal matters, I felt less anxious and depressed. Perhaps there was a sense that everything</description></item><item><title>2022 Year-End Review - Confusion, Low Points and Change</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:18:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Today is the last day of 2022. As I mentioned in my previous weekly review:
There will be an annual summary, covering various events of my year - things lost, things gained, things to be grateful for, and inevitable regrets. Though I hesitated about bringing up certain topics again, I decided to face them truthfully. After all, everything expires, even canned pineapples. This year too shall pass.</description></item><item><title>Why I'm Still Blogging in 2022</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/12/why_i_still_write_blog_in_2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/12/why_i_still_write_blog_in_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Recently, I published several articles introducing my blog setup process and components. Many friends followed my tutorial and set up their own blogs. Meanwhile, some friends raised questions: In 2022, with so many mature writing and publishing platforms available, why do we still go to such lengths to set up and update our own blogs?
I started writing on WeChat Official Account in my freshman year (2015), sharing articles about books, movies, and personal life.</description></item><item><title>Confessions at 23: Seeking Meaning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</guid><description>Confessions of a 23-Year-Old: Seeking Meaning Today is June 6, 2020, and I am 23 years old. This age seems to be an awkward existence. If defined by life stages, my undergraduate graduation is already a year behind, yet it&amp;rsquo;s still too early for two zodiac years. My life experience is far from sufficient to offer advice to others, but I still want to write something to account for my past few years.</description></item></channel></rss>