<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>github action on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/github-action/</link><description>Recent content in github action on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:39:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/github-action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo + GitHub Action: Building Your Automated Blog Publishing System</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:39:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface In a previous article, &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis)&amp;rdquo;, I mentioned using Hugo, a static site generator, to truly build my personal blog. I made some personal customizations and configurations based on the hugo-theme-den theme from the Hugo open-source community to meet my needs.
My solution primarily consists of the following core components:
Personal blog source repository for version control of blog configurations and all article .</description></item><item><title>Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + Cloudflare Pages + Cusdis)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 01:19:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</guid><description>Preface Pseudoyu is my personal blog website. Initially built using WordPress on my Vultr VPS, it was later migrated to a Tencent Cloud server and registered for improved access speed. However, the publishing process remained cumbersome, and server maintenance incurred significant long-term expenses.
Thus, I continuously explored solutions that could ensure optimal access experience both domestically and internationally while being hosted on platforms that streamline deployment and publishing processes. I&amp;rsquo;ve been constantly refining my blog system setup and publishing workflow.</description></item></channel></rss>