<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>serverless on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/serverless/</link><description>Recent content in serverless on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:42 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/serverless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up a Website Analytics System with GoatCounter and Zeabur</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/06/deploy_web_statistics_system_using_goatcounter_and_zeabur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/06/deploy_web_statistics_system_using_goatcounter_and_zeabur/</guid><description>Preface In my article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects. I also started this series of tutorials to document the entire process of setup and deployment.
This article focuses on the analytics system solution.
Analytics System Solution Compared to the blog itself and the commenting system, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t paid much attention to an analytics system for a long time (mainly because there weren&amp;rsquo;t many readers back then).</description></item><item><title>Build Your Free Blog Comment System from Scratch (Remark42 + fly.io)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/22/free_commenting_system_using_remark42_and_flyio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 01:10:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/22/free_commenting_system_using_remark42_and_flyio/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects, and also started this series of tutorials to document the entire process of building and deploying.
This article is about the solution for the commenting system.
Evolution of Commenting Systems I often feel that comments are not just communication between readers and authors, but the content itself is also part of the article.</description></item><item><title>Adding Privacy and Copyright Protection to Your Image Hosting with WebP Cloud and Cloudflare WAF</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;Building Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)&amp;rdquo;, I constructed a free image hosting system using Cloudflare R2 and optimized images through WebP Cloud.
While using WebP Cloud, I discovered it offered features like custom Proxy User Agent and watermarking. This sparked an idea: could I use WebP Cloud to protect the source links of my image hosting, making WebP Cloud&amp;rsquo;s proxy links the sole entry point for accessing all my images, while also uniformly adding my exclusive copyright watermark?</description></item><item><title>How I Rescued Critical Data When My Cloud Server Crashed</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/rescue_my_data_from_a_crashed_server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/rescue_my_data_from_a_crashed_server/</guid><description>Preface On Friday, my 2C2G server purchased from BandwagonHost suddenly reported a kernel error, making it impossible to connect via SSH or restart. After a series of circuitous rescue attempts, I finally managed to salvage over a thousand images from my image hosting service. Still shaken by the experience, I&amp;rsquo;d like to document the rescue process and, incidentally, discuss the new image hosting solution I&amp;rsquo;ve set up.
Server Rescue This server had been running stably for about a year and a half, hosting many of my critical services, including over a thousand irreplaceable images for my blog&amp;rsquo;s image hosting service, persistently stored on the host via Docker Volume.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects, and also started this series of tutorials to document the entire build and deployment process.
This article is about the solution for the image hosting system.
[2024-07-02 Update]
I wrote a new tutorial implementing privacy and copyright protection for the image hosting system, which can be considered an additional chapter.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #25 - Personal Information Output and Synchronization System Based on Crossbell (Refactored)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:12:56 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from January 1, 2023 to January 9, 2023. This is the first weekly review of 2023. Although the New Year feels like it was just yesterday, the first week of January has already ended. Perhaps my psychological perception of time has become increasingly dull. During the New Year, I wrote a rather detailed annual summary,</description></item><item><title>Hugo + GitHub Action: Building Your Automated Blog Publishing System</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:39:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface In a previous article, &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis)&amp;rdquo;, I mentioned using Hugo, a static site generator, to truly build my personal blog. I made some personal customizations and configurations based on the hugo-theme-den theme from the Hugo open-source community to meet my needs.
My solution primarily consists of the following core components:
Personal blog source repository for version control of blog configurations and all article .</description></item><item><title>Lightweight Open Source Free Blog Comment System Solution (Cusdis + Railway)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/24/free_and_lightweight_blog_comment_system_using_cusdis_and_railway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:47:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/24/free_and_lightweight_blog_comment_system_using_cusdis_and_railway/</guid><description>《Here, After Us - Mayday》 Preface Previously, I wrote an article titled &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis),&amp;rdquo; detailing my blog system built using Serverless and some open-source projects. I also started a series to document the setup process.
This article focuses on the blog comment system solution. The earliest comment system I used was the notorious Disqus, a cumbersome system known for collecting user privacy data.</description></item><item><title>Building a Free Personal Blog Analytics System from Scratch (umami + Vercel + Heroku)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/21/free_blog_analysis_using_umami_vercel_and_heroku/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:56:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/21/free_blog_analysis_using_umami_vercel_and_heroku/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Previously, I wrote an article titled &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis)&amp;rdquo;, detailing my blog system built using Serverless and some open-source projects. I also started a series to document the setup process.
A few days ago, I came across an article by Reorx titled &amp;ldquo;Deploy umami for Personal Website Analytics&amp;rdquo;. He introduced the umami project and demonstrated its serverless deployment using Railway.</description></item><item><title>Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + Cloudflare Pages + Cusdis)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 01:19:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</guid><description>Preface Pseudoyu is my personal blog website. Initially built using WordPress on my Vultr VPS, it was later migrated to a Tencent Cloud server and registered for improved access speed. However, the publishing process remained cumbersome, and server maintenance incurred significant long-term expenses.
Thus, I continuously explored solutions that could ensure optimal access experience both domestically and internationally while being hosted on platforms that streamline deployment and publishing processes. I&amp;rsquo;ve been constantly refining my blog system setup and publishing workflow.</description></item></channel></rss>