<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>front-end on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/front-end/</link><description>Recent content in front-end on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:51:11 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/front-end/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #31 - Open Source, Front-end Development and ChatGPT Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:51:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from February 13, 2023 to February 20, 2023.
This week was exceptionally full with work and various personal projects. Although I wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly busy to the point of having no time to sleep, I developed an inexplicable sense of anxiety and low mood, often leading to a tendency for revenge bedtime procrastination.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #23 - How to Learn a New Technology (A Liberal Arts Major's Perspective on Coding)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:20:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Brand New Day - Theme song from Flying Colors&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from December 14 to December 19, 2022. This week I continued working from home due to the pandemic (I feel like I can remove this opening line soon, as it has become the norm). I&amp;rsquo;m still &amp;ldquo;slacking off&amp;rdquo; by learning front-end development, while occasionally writing some back-end code for work. On</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #22 - Involution and Anxiety</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:24:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-12-07 to 2022-12-13.
It&amp;rsquo;s been about 20 cumulative days since I last stepped out of my home. Given the current workload of multiple concurrent projects and the almost-cleared negative status, I haven&amp;rsquo;t planned to return to the office yet. I&amp;rsquo;m even considering staying at home until before the new year. The self-quarantine life is quite pleasant.</description></item></channel></rss>