<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>readwise on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/readwise/</link><description>Recent content in readwise on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:38:39 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/readwise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Persönliches Informationsabruf- und Wissensmanagement-System (Heptabase + Logseq + Readwise)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/05/my_personal_pkm_input_output_system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/05/my_personal_pkm_input_output_system/</guid><description>Vorwort Ich scheine schon immer die Tendenz gehabt zu haben, mich selbst als Maschine zu betrachten, mich oft aus der Perspektive eines Außenstehenden zu beobachten, verschiedene Module zu integrieren und ständig zu basteln und zu optimieren. Wenn sich ein bestimmtes Verhaltensmuster oder eine Gewohnheit, die ich aufgebaut habe, plötzlich in einem bestimmten Moment als nützlich erweist, empfinde ich ein Gefühl der Freude. Umgekehrt, wenn äußere Einflüsse oder mein eigener Zustand das System stören, erlebe ich ein tiefes Unbehagen durch den Zusammenbruch der Ordnung.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #45 - Reading Notes, Knowledge Management, and Life in Two Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from August 16 to September 4, 2023.
Time has flown by, and two to three weeks have passed unnoticed. I comfort myself by saying that shifting each post forward by a week will soon restore the weekly updates. However, these weeks have not been idle. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some books, perused several articles that greatly impacted me, participated in some interesting activities, tinkered with many intriguing things, rebuilt my knowledge management system, and made orderly progress in both my main work and additional interests.</description></item></channel></rss>