<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ego on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/ego/</link><description>Recent content in ego on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/ego/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #12 - Cyberspace, Self-Definition and Boundaries</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/19/weekly_review_20220919/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/19/weekly_review_20220919/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-13 to 2022-09-18.
The past week has been somewhat busy, oscillating between several projects, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much input. I had to work over the weekend but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to stay cooped up at home, so I went out and unexpectedly found a nice café where I spent a pleasant day.
Cyberspace I previously learned about the concept of &amp;ldquo;cyberspace&amp;rdquo; from Reorx&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;Using Automated Workflows to Aggregate Information Intake and Output&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #06 - Sincerity, Games, and Self-Adjustment</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:28:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-01 to 2022-08-07. In terms of work rhythm, it was far from busy, and I even got home as early as 7 p.m. on several days, which was rare. The extra leisure time allowed me to think more about my personality and state of life, and to organize many previously scattered thoughts.</description></item></channel></rss>