<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>programming on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/programming/</link><description>Recent content in programming on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #67 - Reshaping My Information Input System with Follow</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-07-31 to 2024-08-04.
The most delightful experience this week was trying out Follow, an application that excited me after a long while. I compared it with Readwise and decided to cancel my subscription. I also implemented a self-hosted Web Archive solution, and it felt great to eat my own dog food. I continued working on the wall mural with my senior, and there were many other interesting happenings.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #66 - 10x Engineers, Technical Passion and Personal Toolkit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from 2024-07-22 to 2024-07-30.
After an exceptionally rich Adventure X week of activities, I&amp;rsquo;ve returned to the daily routine of coding with focused attention. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with work requirements; continuing to develop the API portion of EpubKit using Cloudflare Worker; refactoring the backend of a side project I started over a year ago but never fully realized using Go, and beginning to attempt writing an API server in Rust; created an Astro web project &amp;ldquo;tools.</description></item><item><title>Docker Fundamentals and Practices</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 01:30:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface This is the first article in the container section of the work practice series, primarily introducing the basic knowledge and practices of Docker. As a backend developer, when I first started working, I mainly debugged locally and hadn&amp;rsquo;t really learned about Docker usage. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until later when I began to engage with more complex underlying chain development</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL Basics and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 23:30:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about organizing and summarizing the technical points and tools commonly used in my work. On one hand, this helps me review these knowledge points and deepen my memory of their usage. On the other hand, it can serve as a reference for future use. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m planning to cover several core areas including databases,</description></item><item><title>Go Error Handling Summary and Best Practices</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/08/29/go_error_handling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:19:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/08/29/go_error_handling/</guid><description>Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been reviewing and summarizing the Go Advanced Training Camp by Mr. Mao Jian from GeekTime. This is a course that leans more towards engineering and principles, covering a wide range of knowledge points. Therefore, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start a series to record and summarize, which will also facilitate my own review and reference. This is the first article in the series, &amp;ldquo;Go Error Handling&amp;rdquo;.
Go Error Handling Mechanism Go Built-in Errors In Go, an error is simply a regular interface representing a value:</description></item><item><title>MySQL Fundamentals and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:12:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</guid><description>Preface Databases are commonly used in both foundational learning and real enterprise business scenarios. There&amp;rsquo;s often a jest that daily work always revolves around CRUD operations. Proficiency in using mainstream relational databases is a fundamental skill for developers. This article will provide an overview of the basic knowledge and related operations of MySQL, a popular relational database, on the MacOS system for easy reference.
Overview of Data and Databases Data Fundamentally, data is a type of fact or observed result, a logical summary of objective matters, and a form and carrier of information.</description></item></channel></rss>