<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>relationship on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/relationship/</link><description>Recent content in relationship on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:39:12 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/relationship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #27 - What Makes a Home</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:39:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-01-16 to 2023-01-22.
This week, my time was equally divided between Beijing, Hangzhou, and my hometown in Jiangsu, traveling back and forth. For someone who hasn&amp;rsquo;t left home for almost three months, the journey brought some fatigue, but I found that I&amp;rsquo;m not actually averse to such a long-standing change in my life rhythm, and even feel some novelty and anticipation.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #19 - Remembering a Startup Experience</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 21:25:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 9, 2022 to November 17, 2022.
I almost missed this week&amp;rsquo;s review. It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I published on time on Sundays (and it&amp;rsquo;s getting later and later). There are always various things happening. I often comfort myself that it&amp;rsquo;s just a record of my life, and I can lower its priority when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #18 - Companionship and Another Way of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:04:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-11-01 to 2022-11-08.
This week marked the first week of living with my cat. Due to the Double 11 shopping festival, I bought many cat facilities and food. With numerous deliveries arriving, I spent about half of my time working from home and receiving packages, which allowed for more bonding time. The cat is incredibly well-behaved.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #17 - Him and His Cat</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:46:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 28 to October 31, 2022.
As the previous weekly review was updated quite late, this period seems particularly brief in its time span. However, it holds special significance due to a major change that entered my life.
After a three-day journey to cat shelters from Friday to Sunday, filled with indecision, I brought home a silver point (silver shaded colorpoint?</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #04 - Vacation, Family Bonds and Sense of Belonging in Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 23:31:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here, After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 11, 2022 to July 24, 2022. As for the reason for the delay - I was on vacation!!!
Vacation Including my internship, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for over a year now, but because projects have been ongoing, I&amp;rsquo;ve had hardly any complete holidays except for the Spring Festival, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated quite a few compensatory days off.</description></item></channel></rss>