<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>love on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/love/</link><description>Recent content in love on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #59 - Desert Journey, Family and Kin</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from May 1st to May 15th, 2024.
During the May Day holiday, I traveled to Inner Mongolia with my family. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until we set off that I realized this was the first time we had ventured on a distant journey together. Previously, our furthest excursion had been a drive to Shanghai Disneyland. It was quite a different experience.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #54 - Drifting Plan, Stolen Wallet, and Home Server</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-03-01 to 2024-03-16.
As mentioned in the previous weekly review, I embarked on a drifting plan, which concluded with a nearly two-week journey through &amp;ldquo;Hangzhou -&amp;gt; Shanghai -&amp;gt; Huzhou -&amp;gt; Nanjing -&amp;gt; Beijing&amp;rdquo;. Mostly confined to Jiangsu and Zhejiang, there weren&amp;rsquo;t any extraordinary landscapes; it was more about people and events. Due to my main wallet being stolen without determining the cause, I reinstalled two primary computers, which provided an opportunity to reorganize my development environment configuration.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #53 - Three Blank Months, Life Adrift, and Spring Festival</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 19:13:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 4, 2023, to February 29, 2024. Much has transpired over the past few months, across various dimensions of life, making it challenging to begin writing this weekly review, which was originally intended to document daily life and personal thoughts. It seemed that no single or even two issues could summarize everything, and</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #52 - Self-effacing Personality and Another Perspective on Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:15:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 30, 2023 to December 3, 2023.
On Sunday evening, while organizing various files, I realized upon opening the document that many previous issues were written in the crevices of workdays. Coincidentally, I returned to Hangzhou on Friday night, having more time to myself. I thought about not delaying the weekly review until midweek to avoid rushing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #51 - Admiring Lawrence and Falling Ill</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-11-22 to 2023-11-29.
This week, my senior and I were both confined at home recovering from influenza A, which significantly impacted our work and daily life. I finished recording the podcast I mentioned last time, chatting casually for over an hour. Despite running a fever for two days over the weekend, I struggled to go out on Sunday to attend Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s offline event.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #49 - Burnt Keyboard, Pompeii Myth Exhibition, Health Adjustments and Magical Dreams</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:23:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of life from 2023-11-08 to 2023-11-12.
This week, I returned to a normal rhythm. Work-wise, the main task was discussing and designing solutions, without much coding involved. For another AI-related project, I wrote some backend API code related to smart contracts and call chains. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve written quite a few contracts, opportunities for non-demo projects that string together the entire process are still rare.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #48 - Inner Mongolia Trip, Chiang Mai Digital Nomads, Restarting Weekly Reviews and Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:01:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection on my life from 2023-09-17 to 2023-11-07. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last put pen to paper, almost a month and a half. A lot happened in the first couple of weeks, and there were many things I wanted to record, but I never managed to find a few hours to complete the weekly review. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #47 - Interview, Boxing and Work Status</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/17/weekly_review_20230917/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 18:42:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/17/weekly_review_20230917/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 13 to September 17, 2023.
On Monday, I went to see the long-awaited &amp;ldquo;Oppenheimer&amp;rdquo; - it had been a while since I last went to the cinema. Saturday was spent sketching at the Old Summer Palace, a fully immersive day. Sunday marked my first boxing class at a boxing gym, quite a novel experience.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #46 - Farewell to Long Hair, Weekly Review's Original Intention, and Contract Development</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/13/weekly_review_20230913/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/13/weekly_review_20230913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This article is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-09-05 to 2023-09-13. I concentrated on writing a contract project that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly complex, and also revisited my learning experience and insights on contract development due to an interview with a content creator friend, continuing to produce my series of tutorials. A publishing house contacted me, and I might start writing a technical book, which I&amp;rsquo;m both looking forward to and feeling a bit anxious about.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #45 - Reading Notes, Knowledge Management, and Life in Two Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from August 16 to September 4, 2023.
Time has flown by, and two to three weeks have passed unnoticed. I comfort myself by saying that shifting each post forward by a week will soon restore the weekly updates. However, these weeks have not been idle. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some books, perused several articles that greatly impacted me, participated in some interesting activities, tinkered with many intriguing things, rebuilt my knowledge management system, and made orderly progress in both my main work and additional interests.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #44 - The Silent Workers, xLog and Daily Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:01:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-07-11 to 2023-08-15.
After nearly a month of stagnation, reopening the weekly review document felt somewhat unfamiliar. In truth, many themes I wanted to write about had accumulated, and there were many words I wished to say. Although my output has decreased, my desire to share has not diminished due to changes in my life state.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #43 - In the Mood for Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:22:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Not Spring, Love, or Cherry Blossoms&amp;#39; - HIGH4&amp;amp;IU Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 22 to July 10, 2023.
The past few weeks have been both long and fleeting, filled with numerous events and thoughts I&amp;rsquo;ve been eager to express. Yet, something in the depths of my heart has repeatedly held me back from putting pen to paper. It&amp;rsquo;s as if everything isn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready, and I find myself at a loss for words, wanting to tell a good story but unsure where to begin.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #42 - Views on Love, Life State and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:03:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-06-13 to 2023-06-21.
This week, I traveled to many places and experienced some emotional fluctuations. After returning, I was busy with various trivial matters, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m only now sitting down to write this weekly review.
I went back to Beijing to visit my former company and met with my previous leaders. We discussed many topics including web3, AI, and various technical issues.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #24 - Love Actually</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 20, 2022 to December 27, 2022.
Unconsciously, this is already the 24th article, and the last weekly review of 2022. Sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s this inexplicable sense of ceremony when meaningful events occur at rather round time points, which often makes one particularly happy.
Sometimes the desire to share is just so wondrous.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item><item><title>Confession at 25: A Love Like a Flower Bouquet</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</guid><description>Preface Today is June 6, 2022, and I am 25 years old. In truth, since that article I wrote two years ago on this day, &amp;ldquo;Confessions at 23: Pursuing Meaning,&amp;rdquo; I had intended to write one every year, as a way to account for the year past, whether it was splendid or mundane. Much indeed happened when I was 23, but each time I opened a blank document, I found</description></item></channel></rss>