<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>writing on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/writing/</link><description>Recent content in writing on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:48:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2024: Was hat sich auf meinem Blog verändert</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/29/what_changed_in_my_blog_2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/29/what_changed_in_my_blog_2024/</guid><description>Vorwort Vor zwei Jahren, in dem Beitrag &amp;ldquo;Es ist 2022, lass uns darüber sprechen, warum ich immer noch blogge&amp;rdquo;, erörterte ich die Ursprünge, Absichten und den Aufbau meines Blogs.
Mehr als zwei Jahre sind vergangen. Die ursprüngliche Intention bleibt bestehen, und das Schreiben hat sich fortgesetzt, obwohl ich die geplanten wöchentlichen Aktualisierungen nicht erreicht habe. Dennoch habe ich eine beachtliche Menge an schriftlichen Werken angesammelt.
Nach vielen Erfahrungen scheine ich mich allmählich in einen &amp;ldquo;Wochenrückblick-Blogger&amp;rdquo; verwandelt zu haben, mit Inhalt und Stil, die sich stark verändert haben.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #39 - First COVID Infection, Past Emotions, and Rediscovered Desire to Share</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from May 1, 2023 to May 20, 2023.
As I type this first line, I realize it has been delayed for three weeks. Many interesting things happened during this period, but it seems my desire to share has been gradually fading. I only jotted down some fragmented thoughts in Logseq, and despite several attempts to organize them, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the right approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #30 - Open Source Budget, Writing Motivation, and Humility Towards Technology</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:41:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-07 to 2023-02-12. This week saw little progress in work, yet the time after the New Year seemed to pass particularly quickly. Though it felt like I hadn&amp;rsquo;t accomplished much of value, I found myself in a state of busyness. I</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item></channel></rss>