<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>memory on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/memory/</link><description>Recent content in memory on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:57:44 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/memory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #40 - Open Source Summer, Beyond Code and Vanishing Sleep</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/30/weekly_review_20230530/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:57:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/30/weekly_review_20230530/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-05-21 to 2023-05-29.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until the weekend that I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t gone downstairs at all this week, which seems to have become the norm in my life. However, my efficiency was decent. At work, I researched and learned about some new things, and continued to read documents related to chains and contracts.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #39 - First COVID Infection, Past Emotions, and Rediscovered Desire to Share</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from May 1, 2023 to May 20, 2023.
As I type this first line, I realize it has been delayed for three weeks. Many interesting things happened during this period, but it seems my desire to share has been gradually fading. I only jotted down some fragmented thoughts in Logseq, and despite several attempts to organize them, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the right approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #34 - Don't Stop the Clocks</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 17:29:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-08 to 2023-03-13. This week was primarily focused on work handovers, which wasn&amp;rsquo;t as busy as before, but the pressing time and impending tasks still brought considerable pressure. After all, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave a city I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in for nearly two years. More time was spent on conversations and gatherings,</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #33 - Beijing x Story x Farewell</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:30:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-27 to 2023-03-07. This week has brought significant changes to my life, and for various reasons, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave Beijing. With many things to handle, I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating Twitter and my Telegram channel less frequently, and even GitHub has</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item></channel></rss>