<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>movie on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/movie/</link><description>Recent content in movie on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 21:56:49 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/movie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #29 - Japanese Learning Experience, Steam Deck and Izakaya</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 21:56:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-01 to 2023-02-06.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first week back at work. Since I had been doing some work during the Spring Festival, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t unaccustomed to the work rhythm. However, I often couldn&amp;rsquo;t freely do my own things, which suddenly made me feel pressed for time.
I started revisiting Japanese and was surprised to find that I still remembered a lot.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #13 - The Joy of Stealing Time from a Busy Schedule</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 23:19:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-19 to 2022-09-26.
This week was unusually busy, with several days where I returned home quite late. Yet, strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s during such times that I seem to find more motivation to do more. I finished a book, caught up on many movies and TV series, and accomplished numerous tasks, both big and small.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #11 - Moods, Travels and Serendipities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 5, 2022 to September 12, 2022.
The past week was quite enriching, both during the workdays and the Mid-Autumn Festival holiday. Work gradually became busier but also more interesting; daily life saw some changes, no longer so dull and mundane; I&amp;rsquo;ve grown accustomed to pulling out my Kindle for a few pages even during short car rides of just a few dozen minutes, quickly becoming immersed; going out has become more frequent, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just aimlessly walking the streets.</description></item></channel></rss>