<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>romance on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/romance/</link><description>Recent content in romance on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:42:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/romance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Confession at 27: Growing Up is a Dispiriting Affair</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</guid><description>《Reply 1988 OST》 Preface It&amp;rsquo;s June 6, 2024, and I&amp;rsquo;m 27 years old.
The idea for the weekly review was born on my birthday two years ago. As I mentioned in last year&amp;rsquo;s summary, this is a column and ritual I want to keep up, and it has arrived as promised.
In the first year, I wrote 40 weekly reviews, but last year there were only 20. What decreased wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the quantity, but also my reflections, emotions, and desire for expression.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #57 - Life Elsewhere (Bali Trip)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-04-01 to 2024-04-10.
As I put pen to paper, it&amp;rsquo;s already late May. Unknowingly, two months have slipped by. It&amp;rsquo;s not just the weekly review updates; the multitude of recent events seems to have made it difficult for me to extricate myself from my entire life. But without realizing it myself, this weekly review, a vessel for recording life, has already become a part of me.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #44 - The Silent Workers, xLog and Daily Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:01:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-07-11 to 2023-08-15.
After nearly a month of stagnation, reopening the weekly review document felt somewhat unfamiliar. In truth, many themes I wanted to write about had accumulated, and there were many words I wished to say. Although my output has decreased, my desire to share has not diminished due to changes in my life state.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #43 - In the Mood for Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:22:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Not Spring, Love, or Cherry Blossoms&amp;#39; - HIGH4&amp;amp;IU Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 22 to July 10, 2023.
The past few weeks have been both long and fleeting, filled with numerous events and thoughts I&amp;rsquo;ve been eager to express. Yet, something in the depths of my heart has repeatedly held me back from putting pen to paper. It&amp;rsquo;s as if everything isn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready, and I find myself at a loss for words, wanting to tell a good story but unsure where to begin.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #42 - Views on Love, Life State and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:03:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-06-13 to 2023-06-21.
This week, I traveled to many places and experienced some emotional fluctuations. After returning, I was busy with various trivial matters, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m only now sitting down to write this weekly review.
I went back to Beijing to visit my former company and met with my previous leaders. We discussed many topics including web3, AI, and various technical issues.</description></item><item><title>Confession at 26: The Stone-Pusher</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Confession at 26: The Stone-Pusher It is now June 6, 2023, and I am 26 years old. As I grow older, I no longer feel much ceremony or anticipation for my birthday itself. Yet, it still serves as a milestone, reminding me that another year has passed. Since last year, I decided to leave some words on my birthday and New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, as a way to account for the time that has elapsed.</description></item><item><title>2022 Year-End Review - Confusion, Low Points and Change</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:18:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Today is the last day of 2022. As I mentioned in my previous weekly review:
There will be an annual summary, covering various events of my year - things lost, things gained, things to be grateful for, and inevitable regrets. Though I hesitated about bringing up certain topics again, I decided to face them truthfully. After all, everything expires, even canned pineapples. This year too shall pass.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Report #24 - Love Actually</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 20, 2022 to December 27, 2022.
Unconsciously, this is already the 24th article, and the last weekly report of 2022. Sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s this inexplicable sense of ceremony when meaningful events occur at rather round time points, which often makes one particularly happy.
Sometimes the desire to share is just so wondrous.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #01 - Emotions, Sense of Security, and Living Earnestly</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/28/weekly_review_20220626/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 22:54:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/28/weekly_review_20220626/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface The idea of writing a weekly review had been on my mind since before my birthday. I was initially drawn to the open-source weekly reviews by Xuanwo. On one hand, I aspired to reach a state where I could produce and contribute something every week. On the other hand, I was intrigued by the concept of observing and measuring my life, work, and learning on a weekly scale.</description></item><item><title>Confession at 25: A Love Like a Flower Bouquet</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</guid><description>Preface Today is June 6, 2022, and I am 25 years old. In truth, since that article I wrote two years ago on this day, &amp;ldquo;Confessions at 23: Pursuing Meaning,&amp;rdquo; I had intended to write one every year, as a way to account for the year past, whether it was splendid or mundane. Much indeed happened when I was 23, but each time I opened a blank document, I found</description></item><item><title>Confessions at 23: Seeking Meaning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</guid><description>Confessions of a 23-Year-Old: Seeking Meaning Today is June 6, 2020, and I am 23 years old. This age seems to be an awkward existence. If defined by life stages, my undergraduate graduation is already a year behind, yet it&amp;rsquo;s still too early for two zodiac years. My life experience is far from sufficient to offer advice to others, but I still want to write something to account for my past few years.</description></item></channel></rss>