<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tools on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/tools/</link><description>Recent content in tools on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #67 - Reshaping My Information Input System with Follow</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-07-31 to 2024-08-04.
The most delightful experience this week was trying out Follow, an application that excited me after a long while. I compared it with Readwise and decided to cancel my subscription. I also implemented a self-hosted Web Archive solution, and it felt great to eat my own dog food. I continued working on the wall mural with my senior, and there were many other interesting happenings.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #66 - 10x Engineers, Technical Passion and Personal Toolkit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from 2024-07-22 to 2024-07-30.
After an exceptionally rich Adventure X week of activities, I&amp;rsquo;ve returned to the daily routine of coding with focused attention. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with work requirements; continuing to develop the API portion of EpubKit using Cloudflare Worker; refactoring the backend of a side project I started over a year ago but never fully realized using Go, and beginning to attempt writing an API server in Rust; created an Astro web project &amp;ldquo;tools.</description></item><item><title>Personal Information Retrieval and Knowledge Management System (Heptabase + Logseq + Readwise)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/05/my_personal_pkm_input_output_system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/05/my_personal_pkm_input_output_system/</guid><description>Preface I seem to have always had a tendency to view myself as a machine, often observing myself from an outsider&amp;rsquo;s perspective, integrating various modules, and constantly tinkering and optimizing. When a certain behavioral pattern or habit I&amp;rsquo;ve built suddenly proves useful at a particular moment, I feel a sense of delight. Conversely, when external influences or my own state disrupt the system, I experience a profound discomfort from the breakdown of order.</description></item><item><title>Warp, iTerm2, or Alacritty? My Terminal Tinkering Journey</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/10/my_config_and_beautify_solution_of_macos_terminal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 11:18:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/10/my_config_and_beautify_solution_of_macos_terminal/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface As a developer, whether running and debugging code locally or deploying and maintaining projects on remote servers, we can&amp;rsquo;t do without the terminal shown in the image below, which is the black window often seen in sci-fi movies.
Operating systems generally have their default shells, such as &amp;ldquo;Powershell&amp;rdquo; on Windows, and bash or zsh on macOS and Linux systems. Systems with graphical interfaces also come with pre-installed terminal emulators, like &amp;ldquo;Terminal.</description></item><item><title>Thin Client Development Workflow Based on frp Internal Network Penetration</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/05/access_your_local_devices_using_reverse_proxy_tool_frp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 10:00:16 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/05/access_your_local_devices_using_reverse_proxy_tool_frp/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface In my previous project &amp;ldquo;GitHub - Personal Toolbox&amp;rdquo;, I mentioned that I have a Mac Studio that&amp;rsquo;s always on at home and a Raspberry Pi 3b+ microcomputer running Ubuntu. When at home, I usually operate the Mac Studio connected to a monitor or access it via SSH from my Chromebook terminal.
After ending remote work, I need to commute between the office and home daily.</description></item><item><title>Personal Toolkit (May 2022)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/08/personal_tools_in_2022_may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 15:47:16 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/08/personal_tools_in_2022_may/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a tool enthusiast, firmly believing in the principle &amp;ldquo;to do a good job, one must first sharpen one&amp;rsquo;s tools.&amp;rdquo; I constantly tinker with and optimize my hardware and software, seeking the best solution for each specific need. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve gradually found solutions that best suit my usage habits. Due to work, study, and personal interests, my devices have gone through many iterations.</description></item></channel></rss>