<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personality on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/personality/</link><description>Recent content in personality on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:15:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/personality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wochenrückblick #52 - Selbstverleugnende Persönlichkeit und eine andere Perspektive auf die Liebe</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:15:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Vorwort Dies ist eine Aufzeichnung und Reflexion meines Lebens vom 30. November 2023 bis zum 3. Dezember 2023.
Am Sonntagabend, während ich verschiedene Dateien ordnete, wurde mir beim Öffnen des Dokuments bewusst, dass viele der vorherigen Ausgaben in den Nischen der Arbeitstage geschrieben wurden. Zufälligerweise kehrte ich am Freitagabend nach Hangzhou zurück und hatte mehr Zeit für mich. Ich dachte darüber nach, den Wochenrückblick nicht bis zur Wochenmitte zu verzögern, um Hektik zu vermeiden.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item></channel></rss>