<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>study on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/study/</link><description>Recent content in study on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:21:15 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wochenrückblick #35 - Zeitungsartikel, Umzug und eine kranke Nini</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:21:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Vorwort Dieser Beitrag ist eine Aufzeichnung und Reflexion meines Lebens vom 14.03.2023 bis zum 23.03.2023.
Wenn es nicht den Anreiz von xLog gäbe, hätte ich diesen Wochenrückblick vielleicht ausgelassen.
In der vergangenen Woche ereignete sich eine Reihe von Vorfällen: Nini erkrankte, meine Eltern fuhren nach Peking, um die Katze (und mich) abzuholen, ich begleitete sie bei der Besichtigung (obwohl es auch für mich das erste Mal bei allen Sehenswürdigkeiten war), traf mich mit Freunden zum Abschied, ertrug eine 15-stündige Reise zwischen den Städten, fand eine neue Wohnung (wobei die Unterzeichnung des Mietvertrags nur eine Stunde dauerte), zog um und richtete die neue Bleibe ein und begann einen neuen Job.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #23 - How to Learn a New Technology (A Liberal Arts Major's Perspective on Coding)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:20:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Brand New Day - Theme song from Flying Colors&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from December 14 to December 19, 2022. This week I continued working from home due to the pandemic (I feel like I can remove this opening line soon, as it has become the norm). I&amp;rsquo;m still &amp;ldquo;slacking off&amp;rdquo; by learning front-end development, while occasionally writing some back-end code for work. On</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #16 - Pure Learning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:28:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from October 19 to October 27, 2022.
This week has been busy with work projects, with several consecutive days of overtime, but I&amp;rsquo;ve finally completed my part of the requirements. However, during the spare moments, I managed to go through introductory tutorials for several languages I&amp;rsquo;ve long wanted to learn, which was quite interesting.</description></item></channel></rss>