<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>learn on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/learn/</link><description>Recent content in learn on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #62 - Hong Kong Trip, 5am Club Plan, and Learning Rust</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/23/weekly_review_20240623/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/23/weekly_review_20240623/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 17, 2024 to June 23, 2024.
I went to Hong Kong to attend the Google AI+Web3 event and met many colleagues from my team in person; experienced sleeping in an internet cafe due to not being able to book a room; decided to adjust my life rhythm according to the 5am Club philosophy; started learning Rust for the second time; and many other interesting things happened.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #50 - A Stroll in the Temple of Heaven, Rediscovering Reading, and the Feynman Technique</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 13 to November 21, 2023.
This week had quite a bit of discussion and development at work, maintaining a normal rhythm. My days were largely occupied by work, study, and additional reading, giving me a sense of fulfillment. As I plan to spend more evenings reading books, I hurried to finish the few dramas and anime I was watching.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #16 - Pure Learning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:28:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from October 19 to October 27, 2022.
This week has been busy with work projects, with several consecutive days of overtime, but I&amp;rsquo;ve finally completed my part of the requirements. However, during the spare moments, I managed to go through introductory tutorials for several languages I&amp;rsquo;ve long wanted to learn, which was quite interesting.</description></item></channel></rss>