<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>backend on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/backend/</link><description>Recent content in backend on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 01:30:48 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/backend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docker Fundamentals and Practices</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 01:30:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface This is the first article in the container section of the work practice series, primarily introducing the basic knowledge and practices of Docker. As a backend developer, when I first started working, I mainly debugged locally and hadn&amp;rsquo;t really learned about Docker usage. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until later when I began to engage with more complex underlying chain development</description></item><item><title>PostgreSQL Basics and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 23:30:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about organizing and summarizing the technical points and tools commonly used in my work. On one hand, this helps me review these knowledge points and deepen my memory of their usage. On the other hand, it can serve as a reference for future use. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m planning to cover several core areas including databases,</description></item><item><title>MySQL Fundamentals and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:12:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</guid><description>Preface Databases are commonly used in both foundational learning and real enterprise business scenarios. There&amp;rsquo;s often a jest that daily work always revolves around CRUD operations. Proficiency in using mainstream relational databases is a fundamental skill for developers. This article will provide an overview of the basic knowledge and related operations of MySQL, a popular relational database, on the MacOS system for easy reference.
Overview of Data and Databases Data Fundamentally, data is a type of fact or observed result, a logical summary of objective matters, and a form and carrier of information.</description></item></channel></rss>