<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>friendship on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/friendship/</link><description>Recent content in friendship on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/friendship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #36 - Gastroenteritis, Nini's Update, and New Journeys</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-25 to 2023-04-02.
Never did I imagine that as a southerner who lived in Hangzhou for over a decade, I would suffer severe adaptation issues upon returning to live in Hangzhou.
In the previous post, I mentioned that Nini was a bit sick due to the bumpy journey and other factors.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #05 - Work, Sense of Time Control, and New Friends</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 23:55:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 25, 2022, to July 31, 2022, also the first week back to work after a vacation.
After experiencing a rare &amp;ldquo;short summer break,&amp;rdquo; I was immediately thrust into the tense preparation of a new project before I had time to adjust my state, which also prompted me to think more about the balance between work and life.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #03 - Health, Goals and the Rhythm of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:30:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface It seems that every time I start with the title, I try to set a theme for the past week. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s not that easy to summarize, but I still persist in doing so. Perhaps this way, life will be like a series of chapters pieced together, and when looking back after a long time, it will feel like a fulfilling book.
This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-07-04 to 2022-07-10.</description></item></channel></rss>