<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>time on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/time/</link><description>Recent content in time on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:01:24 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #44 - The Silent Workers, xLog and Daily Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:01:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-07-11 to 2023-08-15.
After nearly a month of stagnation, reopening the weekly review document felt somewhat unfamiliar. In truth, many themes I wanted to write about had accumulated, and there were many words I wished to say. Although my output has decreased, my desire to share has not diminished due to changes in my life state.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #43 - In the Mood for Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:22:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Not Spring, Love, or Cherry Blossoms&amp;#39; - HIGH4&amp;amp;IU Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 22 to July 10, 2023.
The past few weeks have been both long and fleeting, filled with numerous events and thoughts I&amp;rsquo;ve been eager to express. Yet, something in the depths of my heart has repeatedly held me back from putting pen to paper. It&amp;rsquo;s as if everything isn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready, and I find myself at a loss for words, wanting to tell a good story but unsure where to begin.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #42 - Views on Love, Life State and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:03:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-06-13 to 2023-06-21.
This week, I traveled to many places and experienced some emotional fluctuations. After returning, I was busy with various trivial matters, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m only now sitting down to write this weekly review.
I went back to Beijing to visit my former company and met with my previous leaders. We discussed many topics including web3, AI, and various technical issues.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #41 - Birthday Rituals, Time Management, and a Trip to Beijing</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:50:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from May 30, 2023 to June 12, 2023. On the first day of June, I told a friend, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m usually quite miserable every May, June will definitely be my lucky month.&amp;rdquo; Whether it was a psychological effect or the power of will, these two weeks after entering June have seen improvements in various aspects. I</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #34 - Don't Stop the Clocks</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 17:29:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-08 to 2023-03-13. This week was primarily focused on work handovers, which wasn&amp;rsquo;t as busy as before, but the pressing time and impending tasks still brought considerable pressure. After all, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave a city I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in for nearly two years. More time was spent on conversations and gatherings,</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #13 - The Joy of Stealing Time from a Busy Schedule</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 23:19:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-19 to 2022-09-26.
This week was unusually busy, with several days where I returned home quite late. Yet, strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s during such times that I seem to find more motivation to do more. I finished a book, caught up on many movies and TV series, and accomplished numerous tasks, both big and small.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #07 - Learning, Certification and Career Pursuit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 12:36:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-08 to 2022-08-15. This week&amp;rsquo;s work still revolved around preparing for an evaluation of the project, mainly focusing on explaining the proposal. Work hours were relatively normal, and I gradually regained a good life rhythm.
However, I felt that after getting used to staying at home after work, I lacked the motivation to go out.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #06 - Sincerity, Games, and Self-Adjustment</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:28:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-01 to 2022-08-07. In terms of work rhythm, it was far from busy, and I even got home as early as 7 p.m. on several days, which was rare. The extra leisure time allowed me to think more about my personality and state of life, and to organize many previously scattered thoughts.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #05 - Work, Sense of Time Control, and New Friends</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 23:55:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 25, 2022, to July 31, 2022, also the first week back to work after a vacation.
After experiencing a rare &amp;ldquo;short summer break,&amp;rdquo; I was immediately thrust into the tense preparation of a new project before I had time to adjust my state, which also prompted me to think more about the balance between work and life.</description></item></channel></rss>