<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>city on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/city/</link><description>Recent content in city on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #59 - Desert Journey, Family and Kin</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from May 1st to May 15th, 2024.
During the May Day holiday, I traveled to Inner Mongolia with my family. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until we set off that I realized this was the first time we had ventured on a distant journey together. Previously, our furthest excursion had been a drive to Shanghai Disneyland. It was quite a different experience.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #58 - A Year of Remote Work</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from April 10, 2024 to April 30, 2024.
It&amp;rsquo;s already mid-April since returning from Bali, welcoming another major change in life - moving back to Hangzhou from Beijing once again and renting a new place. The rhythm of life has subtly shifted as a result. Coincidentally, it&amp;rsquo;s been a year since I last moved back to Hangzhou, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to discuss my year of remote work in this piece.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #45 - Reading Notes, Knowledge Management, and Life in Two Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from August 16 to September 4, 2023.
Time has flown by, and two to three weeks have passed unnoticed. I comfort myself by saying that shifting each post forward by a week will soon restore the weekly updates. However, these weeks have not been idle. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some books, perused several articles that greatly impacted me, participated in some interesting activities, tinkered with many intriguing things, rebuilt my knowledge management system, and made orderly progress in both my main work and additional interests.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #37 - A Fortnight of Leisure (Wuhan | Hong Kong | Mayday)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:39:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from April 3rd to April 18th, 2023.
Perhaps due to my recent change in lifestyle, I had planned numerous engagements as early as March. From the beginning of April, I found myself wandering, experiencing a fortnight of leisure. This journey was akin to a homecoming - departing from Hangzhou where I was raised, to Wuhan, the first place I left home for an extended period, to visit my professor and old friends, and finally to Hong Kong, where I spent some remarkable years, to attend exhibitions and events.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #36 - Gastroenteritis, Nini's Update, and New Journeys</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-25 to 2023-04-02.
Never did I imagine that as a southerner who lived in Hangzhou for over a decade, I would suffer severe adaptation issues upon returning to live in Hangzhou.
In the previous post, I mentioned that Nini was a bit sick due to the bumpy journey and other factors.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #35 - Newspaper Feature, Moving, and a Sick Nini</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:21:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-14 to 2023-03-23.
If it weren&amp;rsquo;t for xLog&amp;rsquo;s incentive, I might have skipped this weekly review.
In the past week or so, a series of events unfolded: Nini fell ill, my parents drove to Beijing to pick up the cat (and me), I accompanied them sightseeing (though it was my first time at all the attractions too), met with friends before parting ways, endured a 15-hour cross-city journey, found a new apartment (though it only took an hour to sign the lease), moved and decorated the new place, and started a new job.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #33 - Beijing x Story x Farewell</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:30:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-27 to 2023-03-07. This week has brought significant changes to my life, and for various reasons, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave Beijing. With many things to handle, I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating Twitter and my Telegram channel less frequently, and even GitHub has</description></item><item><title>Fotografiesammlung #02 - Moment in Peking (Der Herbst)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/01/02/moment_in_peking_the_autumn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/01/02/moment_in_peking_the_autumn/</guid><description>Vorwort Es ist über ein Jahr her, seit ich nach Peking gekommen bin. Aufgrund langer Perioden, in denen ich in meinem kleinen Zimmer verweilte und mir die Stimmung zum Erkunden fehlte, beschränkten sich die vier Jahreszeiten lediglich auf das wechselnde Grün auf meinem Arbeitsweg. Ich habe nicht einmal die bekanntesten Wahrzeichen besucht.
Tatsächlich bin ich über die Jahre zwischen einigen Städten umgezogen. Jedes Mal dachte ich: &amp;ldquo;Es ist noch Zeit&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Es liegen noch viele Tage vor mir&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Es wird immer eine Gelegenheit geben&amp;rdquo;, und doch blieben oft viele Bedauern zurück.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #04 - Vacation, Family Bonds and Sense of Belonging in Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 23:31:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here, After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 11, 2022 to July 24, 2022. As for the reason for the delay - I was on vacation!!!
Vacation Including my internship, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for over a year now, but because projects have been ongoing, I&amp;rsquo;ve had hardly any complete holidays except for the Spring Festival, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated quite a few compensatory days off.</description></item></channel></rss>