<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>consensus on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/consensus/</link><description>Recent content in consensus on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 20:00:03 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/consensus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cosmos Blockchain Architecture and Tendermint Consensus Mechanism</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/10/cosmos_introduction_and_explaination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 20:00:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/10/cosmos_introduction_and_explaination/</guid><description>Preface In my work, I am primarily involved in the architectural design and implementation of cross-chain projects. As our company&amp;rsquo;s existing solution is based on the Cosmos blockchain, I have spent over a year working on some underlying chain development modifications using the Cosmos SDK. This has given me some understanding of its technical implementation. However, due to the tight development schedule, I never had the opportunity to gain a systematic understanding of Cosmos&amp;rsquo; architectural design and the Tendermint consensus mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Distributed Systems and Blockchain Consensus Mechanisms</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/08/blockchain_consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:03:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/08/blockchain_consensus/</guid><description>Preface As internet systems grow increasingly complex, most have shifted from monolithic to distributed architectures. Blockchain technology, which is fundamentally based on distributed systems, heavily relies on data consistency and consensus mechanisms.
This article will introduce the concepts of consistency and consensus in distributed systems, as well as their practical applications and developments in blockchain technology.
Distributed Systems The Consistency Problem As business scenarios become more complex, a single service is often provided by multiple servers forming a cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>