<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cat on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/cat/</link><description>Recent content in cat on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:23:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/cat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #49 - Burnt Keyboard, Pompeii Myth Exhibition, Health Adjustments and Magical Dreams</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:23:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of life from 2023-11-08 to 2023-11-12.
This week, I returned to a normal rhythm. Work-wise, the main task was discussing and designing solutions, without much coding involved. For another AI-related project, I wrote some backend API code related to smart contracts and call chains. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve written quite a few contracts, opportunities for non-demo projects that string together the entire process are still rare.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #48 - Inner Mongolia Trip, Chiang Mai Digital Nomads, Restarting Weekly Reviews and Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:01:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection on my life from 2023-09-17 to 2023-11-07. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last put pen to paper, almost a month and a half. A lot happened in the first couple of weeks, and there were many things I wanted to record, but I never managed to find a few hours to complete the weekly review. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #42 - Views on Love, Life State and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:03:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-06-13 to 2023-06-21.
This week, I traveled to many places and experienced some emotional fluctuations. After returning, I was busy with various trivial matters, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m only now sitting down to write this weekly review.
I went back to Beijing to visit my former company and met with my previous leaders. We discussed many topics including web3, AI, and various technical issues.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #41 - Birthday Rituals, Time Management, and a Trip to Beijing</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:50:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from May 30, 2023 to June 12, 2023. On the first day of June, I told a friend, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m usually quite miserable every May, June will definitely be my lucky month.&amp;rdquo; Whether it was a psychological effect or the power of will, these two weeks after entering June have seen improvements in various aspects. I</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #36 - Gastroenteritis, Nini's Update, and New Journeys</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-25 to 2023-04-02.
Never did I imagine that as a southerner who lived in Hangzhou for over a decade, I would suffer severe adaptation issues upon returning to live in Hangzhou.
In the previous post, I mentioned that Nini was a bit sick due to the bumpy journey and other factors.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #35 - Newspaper Feature, Moving, and a Sick Nini</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:21:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-14 to 2023-03-23.
If it weren&amp;rsquo;t for xLog&amp;rsquo;s incentive, I might have skipped this weekly review.
In the past week or so, a series of events unfolded: Nini fell ill, my parents drove to Beijing to pick up the cat (and me), I accompanied them sightseeing (though it was my first time at all the attractions too), met with friends before parting ways, endured a 15-hour cross-city journey, found a new apartment (though it only took an hour to sign the lease), moved and decorated the new place, and started a new job.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #32 - Wuhan, Long-Awaited Reunions, and Flowing Emotions</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:24:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-21 to 2023-02-26. This week was relatively routine in terms of work, with no particularly urgent tasks. Despite being in a somewhat tense state due to personal matters, I felt less anxious and depressed. Perhaps there was a sense that everything</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #31 - Open Source, Front-end Development and ChatGPT Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:51:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from February 13, 2023 to February 20, 2023.
This week was exceptionally full with work and various personal projects. Although I wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly busy to the point of having no time to sleep, I developed an inexplicable sense of anxiety and low mood, often leading to a tendency for revenge bedtime procrastination.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #30 - Open Source Budget, Writing Motivation, and Humility Towards Technology</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:41:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-07 to 2023-02-12. This week saw little progress in work, yet the time after the New Year seemed to pass particularly quickly. Though it felt like I hadn&amp;rsquo;t accomplished much of value, I found myself in a state of busyness. I</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #29 - Japanese Learning Experience, Steam Deck and Izakaya</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 21:56:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-01 to 2023-02-06.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first week back at work. Since I had been doing some work during the Spring Festival, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t unaccustomed to the work rhythm. However, I often couldn&amp;rsquo;t freely do my own things, which suddenly made me feel pressed for time.
I started revisiting Japanese and was surprised to find that I still remembered a lot.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #28 - Mastodon, Hometown, and Hide-and-Seek Cat</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/31/weekly_review_20230131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:43:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/31/weekly_review_20230131/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-01-23 to 2023-01-31.
I spent most of this week in my hometown, making up for some regrets, simple yet precious. After returning to Hangzhou, I stayed an extra day to meet friends, then hurried back to Beijing from Hangzhou. Upon arriving home in Beijing, I immediately went to pick up Nini from my colleague&amp;rsquo;s house after barely putting down my luggage.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #27 - What Makes a Home</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:39:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-01-16 to 2023-01-22.
This week, my time was equally divided between Beijing, Hangzhou, and my hometown in Jiangsu, traveling back and forth. For someone who hasn&amp;rsquo;t left home for almost three months, the journey brought some fatigue, but I found that I&amp;rsquo;m not actually averse to such a long-standing change in my life rhythm, and even feel some novelty and anticipation.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #26 - Blog, Custom Keyboard and New Server</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/15/weekly_review_20230115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:57:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/15/weekly_review_20230115/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from January 10, 2023 to January 15, 2023. The holiday season is approaching, though I don&amp;rsquo;t have much of a sense of ritual for the New Year. Last year, I spent over a week playing through &amp;ldquo;Pokémon Legends: Arceus&amp;rdquo; and revisiting &amp;ldquo;Fire</description></item><item><title>Photography Collection #01 - Cat In The Box</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/01/cat_in_the_box/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:18:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/01/cat_in_the_box/</guid><description>Preface Since November, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to take proper photos of Nini, but the lighting at home isn&amp;rsquo;t ideal. Due to a busy work schedule, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t deliberately purchased backdrop or lighting equipment. Today, while editing the photos (I mainly just adjust the colors, being lazy), I felt the final images weren&amp;rsquo;t entirely satisfactory. However, I can&amp;rsquo;t abandon my New Year&amp;rsquo;s Day resolution, so I asked a friend to select a few photos that seemed acceptable.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #24 - Love Actually</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 20, 2022 to December 27, 2022.
Unconsciously, this is already the 24th article, and the last weekly review of 2022. Sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s this inexplicable sense of ceremony when meaningful events occur at rather round time points, which often makes one particularly happy.
Sometimes the desire to share is just so wondrous.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #23 - How to Learn a New Technology (A Liberal Arts Major's Perspective on Coding)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:20:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Brand New Day - Theme song from Flying Colors&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from December 14 to December 19, 2022. This week I continued working from home due to the pandemic (I feel like I can remove this opening line soon, as it has become the norm). I&amp;rsquo;m still &amp;ldquo;slacking off&amp;rdquo; by learning front-end development, while occasionally writing some back-end code for work. On</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #22 - Involution and Anxiety</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:24:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-12-07 to 2022-12-13.
It&amp;rsquo;s been about 20 cumulative days since I last stepped out of my home. Given the current workload of multiple concurrent projects and the almost-cleared negative status, I haven&amp;rsquo;t planned to return to the office yet. I&amp;rsquo;m even considering staying at home until before the new year. The self-quarantine life is quite pleasant.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #21 - Life Picked Up Again</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/06/weekly_review_20221206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 21:48:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/06/weekly_review_20221206/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-11-28 to 2022-12-06.
They say it takes 21 days to form a habit, yet by the 21st weekly review, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t managed to update on schedule. Each week brings a creative excuse for the delay.
The past week wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly busy work-wise, with features developed for events successfully launched and entering the routine maintenance phase.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #20 - The Loss of Desire to Consume</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:08:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 18 to November 27, 2022.
The weekend has arrived, and for once, I had no concentrated development work. I slept soundly, caught up on some missed episodes in the afternoon, and finally began writing my weekly review. It seems I&amp;rsquo;ve been delaying it for a few days each week, sneakily erasing a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #19 - Remembering a Startup Experience</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 21:25:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 9, 2022 to November 17, 2022.
I almost missed this week&amp;rsquo;s review. It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I published on time on Sundays (and it&amp;rsquo;s getting later and later). There are always various things happening. I often comfort myself that it&amp;rsquo;s just a record of my life, and I can lower its priority when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #18 - Companionship and Another Way of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:04:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-11-01 to 2022-11-08.
This week marked the first week of living with my cat. Due to the Double 11 shopping festival, I bought many cat facilities and food. With numerous deliveries arriving, I spent about half of my time working from home and receiving packages, which allowed for more bonding time. The cat is incredibly well-behaved.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #17 - Him and His Cat</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:46:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 28 to October 31, 2022.
As the previous weekly review was updated quite late, this period seems particularly brief in its time span. However, it holds special significance due to a major change that entered my life.
After a three-day journey to cat shelters from Friday to Sunday, filled with indecision, I brought home a silver point (silver shaded colorpoint?</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item></channel></rss>