<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>devops on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/devops/</link><description>Recent content in devops on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 01:30:48 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docker Fundamentals and Practices</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 01:30:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/07/container_docker_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface This is the first article in the container section of the work practice series, primarily introducing the basic knowledge and practices of Docker. As a backend developer, when I first started working, I mainly debugged locally and hadn&amp;rsquo;t really learned about Docker usage. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until later when I began to engage with more complex underlying chain development</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #07 - Learning, Certification and Career Pursuit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 12:36:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-08 to 2022-08-15. This week&amp;rsquo;s work still revolved around preparing for an evaluation of the project, mainly focusing on explaining the proposal. Work hours were relatively normal, and I gradually regained a good life rhythm.
However, I felt that after getting used to staying at home after work, I lacked the motivation to go out.</description></item><item><title>SonarQube Code Quality Check Tool Configuration</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/10/27/sonarqube_code_check_setup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 01:57:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/10/27/sonarqube_code_check_setup/</guid><description>Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been responsible for managing code repositories and conducting code reviews for some of the company&amp;rsquo;s projects. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using SonarQube, a code quality check tool that, when integrated with GitLab CI, can automatically perform code quality checks and output inspection reports for each merge request or commit.
This article documents the complete configuration process for importing projects through GitLab repositories, serving as a reference for configuring other projects.</description></item></channel></rss>