<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>review on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/review/</link><description>Recent content in review on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #69 - AI Coding Experience and the Source of Learning Motivation</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/19/weekly_review_20240819/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/19/weekly_review_20240819/</guid><description>《Photograph - Ed Sheeran》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from August 12, 2024 to August 18, 2024.
Transitioning from VS Code to Cursor for coding, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my experience with AI-enhanced programming; celebrating 400 days with my senior; a late-night conversation with her about past experiences and hobbies sparked my contemplation on the source of my learning motivation; and many other interesting happenings.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #68 - On Blogging and the Colors of My Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/18/weekly_review_20240818/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/18/weekly_review_20240818/</guid><description>《Photograph - Ed Sheeran》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-08-05 to 2024-08-11.
Looking back at this week through my TG Channel, I realized that the entire week revolved around setting up and writing blogs. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some thoughts and the desire to share, most of which I&amp;rsquo;ve already posted. This is more of a compilation.
The ROI of Blogging A few days ago, I saw some discussions about blogging on Twitter, and then I read Innei&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;From Disliking Writing to Enjoying Sharing: My Journey with Blogging&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #67 - Reshaping My Information Input System with Follow</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/05/weekly_review_20240805/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-07-31 to 2024-08-04.
The most delightful experience this week was trying out Follow, an application that excited me after a long while. I compared it with Readwise and decided to cancel my subscription. I also implemented a self-hosted Web Archive solution, and it felt great to eat my own dog food. I continued working on the wall mural with my senior, and there were many other interesting happenings.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #66 - 10x Engineers, Technical Passion and Personal Toolkit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/30/weekly_review_20240730/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from 2024-07-22 to 2024-07-30.
After an exceptionally rich Adventure X week of activities, I&amp;rsquo;ve returned to the daily routine of coding with focused attention. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with work requirements; continuing to develop the API portion of EpubKit using Cloudflare Worker; refactoring the backend of a side project I started over a year ago but never fully realized using Go, and beginning to attempt writing an API server in Rust; created an Astro web project &amp;ldquo;tools.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #65 - Adventure X Experience, Apple Notes Practice, and EpubKit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/21/weekly_review_20240721/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/21/weekly_review_20240721/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from July 10 to July 21, 2024.
This week and a half has been quite eventful. Work has been somewhat busy. I participated in the Adventure X event, which was a lot of fun. I experimented with the Remix framework and prepared for a workshop. I met with Randy, and together we planned the redesign and subsequent development of EpubKit, essentially holding our own hackathon for us &amp;ldquo;middle-aged hippies&amp;rdquo; who couldn&amp;rsquo;t participate in the competition.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #64 - Life Is Here (Stoner and Normal People)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a reflection on life from July 1st to July 9th, 2024.
This week, I maintained an early rising routine for several days, dedicating time to reading and studying with high efficiency. However, establishing a regular pattern still requires time and adjustment. I&amp;rsquo;m also exploring how to enter and switch work modes more swiftly. I&amp;rsquo;m simultaneously reading several books: &amp;ldquo;Atlas Shrugged&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Normal People&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;What My Bones Know&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #63 - An Unpleasant Flower Ordering Experience, Merchants and Consumers, and the Increasingly AI-like Humans</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from June 24 to June 30, 2024.
An unpleasant flower ordering and rights protection experience led me to ponder the relationship between merchants and consumers, as well as the phenomenon of humans becoming more AI-like while AI becomes increasingly human-like. On Friday, my server suddenly experienced a Kernel Panic and couldn&amp;rsquo;t reboot. After various roundabout rescue attempts, I finally salvaged over a thousand images from the image bed, leaving me feeling quite shaken.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #62 - Hong Kong Trip, 5am Club Plan, and Learning Rust</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/23/weekly_review_20240623/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/23/weekly_review_20240623/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 17, 2024 to June 23, 2024.
I went to Hong Kong to attend the Google AI+Web3 event and met many colleagues from my team in person; experienced sleeping in an internet cafe due to not being able to book a room; decided to adjust my life rhythm according to the 5am Club philosophy; started learning Rust for the second time; and many other interesting things happened.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #61 - A Good Friend's Wedding and Reflections on Marriage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/16/weekly_review_20240616/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/16/weekly_review_20240616/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 7, 2024, to June 16, 2024.
A Good Friend&amp;rsquo;s Wedding I returned to Beijing during the Dragon Boat Festival to attend a wedding - that of my dear high school friend, Jian.
In high school, I was in the liberal arts class with only eight boys. One of them had a sudden epiphany in the second year of high school, deciding to take a break from school to write books and revitalize Chinese literature, leaving only seven of us to accompany each other through the third year.</description></item><item><title>Confession at 27: Growing Up is a Dispiriting Affair</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</guid><description>《Reply 1988 OST》 Preface It&amp;rsquo;s June 6, 2024, and I&amp;rsquo;m 27 years old.
The idea for the weekly review was born on my birthday two years ago. As I mentioned in last year&amp;rsquo;s summary, this is a column and ritual I want to keep up, and it has arrived as promised.
In the first year, I wrote 40 weekly reviews, but last year there were only 20. What decreased wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the quantity, but also my reflections, emotions, and desire for expression.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #60 - Beside Bugs, Educational Philosophy and EpubKit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/02/weekly_review_20240602/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/02/weekly_review_20240602/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from May 16, 2024 to June 2, 2024. Study Tour in Nanjing I had attended several Yixi talks in Beijing before and quite enjoyed their style. By chance, I saw they were organizing a parent-child study tour in Nanjing. One of the arrangements was to visit the studio of designer/writer Zhu Yingchun, whom my senior</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #59 - Desert Journey, Family and Kin</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/05/15/weekly_review_20240515/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from May 1st to May 15th, 2024.
During the May Day holiday, I traveled to Inner Mongolia with my family. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until we set off that I realized this was the first time we had ventured on a distant journey together. Previously, our furthest excursion had been a drive to Shanghai Disneyland. It was quite a different experience.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #58 - A Year of Remote Work</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from April 10, 2024 to April 30, 2024.
It&amp;rsquo;s already mid-April since returning from Bali, welcoming another major change in life - moving back to Hangzhou from Beijing once again and renting a new place. The rhythm of life has subtly shifted as a result. Coincidentally, it&amp;rsquo;s been a year since I last moved back to Hangzhou, so I&amp;rsquo;d like to discuss my year of remote work in this piece.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #57 - Life Elsewhere (Bali Trip)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/04/10/weekly_review_20240410/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-04-01 to 2024-04-10.
As I put pen to paper, it&amp;rsquo;s already late May. Unknowingly, two months have slipped by. It&amp;rsquo;s not just the weekly review updates; the multitude of recent events seems to have made it difficult for me to extricate myself from my entire life. But without realizing it myself, this weekly review, a vessel for recording life, has already become a part of me.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #56 - Meeting Randy and Taking the Driver's Test</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/31/weekly_review_20240331/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/31/weekly_review_20240331/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from March 25, 2024 to March 31, 2024.
The happiest event this week was meeting Randy. My fan dream came true, and we had a delightful conversation. To avoid impacting work, I woke up at 5 AM for four or five consecutive days to practice driving at the school. It was tough, but I passed the second stage of the driver&amp;rsquo;s test in one go - worth it.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #55 - Oil Painting Experience, Blog System Upgrade, and Thoughts on Self-Hosting</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/24/weekly_review_20240324/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/24/weekly_review_20240324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-03-17 to 2024-03-24.
This week, I rekindled much of my enthusiasm for work and learning, completing the long-listed blog comment system and data statistics system migration in my TODO list, giving me a sense of tidying up my desk. Over the weekend, I experienced oil painting for the first time, painting a new avatar for myself, filled with a sense of accomplishment.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #54 - Drifting Plan, Stolen Wallet, and Home Server</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/16/weekly_review_20240316/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-03-01 to 2024-03-16.
As mentioned in the previous weekly review, I embarked on a drifting plan, which concluded with a nearly two-week journey through &amp;ldquo;Hangzhou -&amp;gt; Shanghai -&amp;gt; Huzhou -&amp;gt; Nanjing -&amp;gt; Beijing&amp;rdquo;. Mostly confined to Jiangsu and Zhejiang, there weren&amp;rsquo;t any extraordinary landscapes; it was more about people and events. Due to my main wallet being stolen without determining the cause, I reinstalled two primary computers, which provided an opportunity to reorganize my development environment configuration.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #53 - Three Blank Months, Life Adrift, and Spring Festival</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 19:13:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 4, 2023, to February 29, 2024. Much has transpired over the past few months, across various dimensions of life, making it challenging to begin writing this weekly review, which was originally intended to document daily life and personal thoughts. It seemed that no single or even two issues could summarize everything, and</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #52 - Self-effacing Personality and Another Perspective on Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:15:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 30, 2023 to December 3, 2023.
On Sunday evening, while organizing various files, I realized upon opening the document that many previous issues were written in the crevices of workdays. Coincidentally, I returned to Hangzhou on Friday night, having more time to myself. I thought about not delaying the weekly review until midweek to avoid rushing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #51 - Admiring Lawrence and Falling Ill</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-11-22 to 2023-11-29.
This week, my senior and I were both confined at home recovering from influenza A, which significantly impacted our work and daily life. I finished recording the podcast I mentioned last time, chatting casually for over an hour. Despite running a fever for two days over the weekend, I struggled to go out on Sunday to attend Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s offline event.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #50 - A Stroll in the Temple of Heaven, Rediscovering Reading, and the Feynman Technique</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 13 to November 21, 2023.
This week had quite a bit of discussion and development at work, maintaining a normal rhythm. My days were largely occupied by work, study, and additional reading, giving me a sense of fulfillment. As I plan to spend more evenings reading books, I hurried to finish the few dramas and anime I was watching.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #49 - Burnt Keyboard, Pompeii Myth Exhibition, Health Adjustments and Magical Dreams</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 21:23:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/12/weekly_review_20231112/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of life from 2023-11-08 to 2023-11-12.
This week, I returned to a normal rhythm. Work-wise, the main task was discussing and designing solutions, without much coding involved. For another AI-related project, I wrote some backend API code related to smart contracts and call chains. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve written quite a few contracts, opportunities for non-demo projects that string together the entire process are still rare.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #48 - Inner Mongolia Trip, Chiang Mai Digital Nomads, Restarting Weekly Reviews and Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:01:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/07/weekly_review_20231107/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection on my life from 2023-09-17 to 2023-11-07. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I last put pen to paper, almost a month and a half. A lot happened in the first couple of weeks, and there were many things I wanted to record, but I never managed to find a few hours to complete the weekly review. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #47 - Interview, Boxing and Work Status</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/17/weekly_review_20230917/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 18:42:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/17/weekly_review_20230917/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 13 to September 17, 2023.
On Monday, I went to see the long-awaited &amp;ldquo;Oppenheimer&amp;rdquo; - it had been a while since I last went to the cinema. Saturday was spent sketching at the Old Summer Palace, a fully immersive day. Sunday marked my first boxing class at a boxing gym, quite a novel experience.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #46 - Farewell to Long Hair, Weekly Review's Original Intention, and Contract Development</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/13/weekly_review_20230913/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/13/weekly_review_20230913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This article is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-09-05 to 2023-09-13. I concentrated on writing a contract project that wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly complex, and also revisited my learning experience and insights on contract development due to an interview with a content creator friend, continuing to produce my series of tutorials. A publishing house contacted me, and I might start writing a technical book, which I&amp;rsquo;m both looking forward to and feeling a bit anxious about.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #45 - Reading Notes, Knowledge Management, and Life in Two Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:58:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/09/04/weekly_review_20230904/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from August 16 to September 4, 2023.
Time has flown by, and two to three weeks have passed unnoticed. I comfort myself by saying that shifting each post forward by a week will soon restore the weekly updates. However, these weeks have not been idle. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some books, perused several articles that greatly impacted me, participated in some interesting activities, tinkered with many intriguing things, rebuilt my knowledge management system, and made orderly progress in both my main work and additional interests.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #44 - The Silent Workers, xLog and Daily Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:01:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/08/15/weekly_review_20230815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-07-11 to 2023-08-15.
After nearly a month of stagnation, reopening the weekly review document felt somewhat unfamiliar. In truth, many themes I wanted to write about had accumulated, and there were many words I wished to say. Although my output has decreased, my desire to share has not diminished due to changes in my life state.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #43 - In the Mood for Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:22:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/07/10/weekly_review_20230710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Not Spring, Love, or Cherry Blossoms&amp;#39; - HIGH4&amp;amp;IU Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from June 22 to July 10, 2023.
The past few weeks have been both long and fleeting, filled with numerous events and thoughts I&amp;rsquo;ve been eager to express. Yet, something in the depths of my heart has repeatedly held me back from putting pen to paper. It&amp;rsquo;s as if everything isn&amp;rsquo;t quite ready, and I find myself at a loss for words, wanting to tell a good story but unsure where to begin.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #42 - Views on Love, Life State and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 10:03:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/21/weekly_review_20230621/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-06-13 to 2023-06-21.
This week, I traveled to many places and experienced some emotional fluctuations. After returning, I was busy with various trivial matters, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m only now sitting down to write this weekly review.
I went back to Beijing to visit my former company and met with my previous leaders. We discussed many topics including web3, AI, and various technical issues.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #41 - Birthday Rituals, Time Management, and a Trip to Beijing</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:50:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/12/weekly_review_20230612/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from May 30, 2023 to June 12, 2023. On the first day of June, I told a friend, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m usually quite miserable every May, June will definitely be my lucky month.&amp;rdquo; Whether it was a psychological effect or the power of will, these two weeks after entering June have seen improvements in various aspects. I</description></item><item><title>Confession at 26: The Stone-Pusher</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Confession at 26: The Stone-Pusher It is now June 6, 2023, and I am 26 years old. As I grow older, I no longer feel much ceremony or anticipation for my birthday itself. Yet, it still serves as a milestone, reminding me that another year has passed. Since last year, I decided to leave some words on my birthday and New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve, as a way to account for the time that has elapsed.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #40 - Open Source Summer, Beyond Code and Vanishing Sleep</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/30/weekly_review_20230530/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:57:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/30/weekly_review_20230530/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-05-21 to 2023-05-29.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until the weekend that I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t gone downstairs at all this week, which seems to have become the norm in my life. However, my efficiency was decent. At work, I researched and learned about some new things, and continued to read documents related to chains and contracts.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #39 - First COVID Infection, Past Emotions, and Rediscovered Desire to Share</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from May 1, 2023 to May 20, 2023.
As I type this first line, I realize it has been delayed for three weeks. Many interesting things happened during this period, but it seems my desire to share has been gradually fading. I only jotted down some fragmented thoughts in Logseq, and despite several attempts to organize them, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the right approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #38 - Foundry Contract Testing, Logseq Task Management, and Surge Ponte Remote Development</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/30/weekly_review_20230430/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:10:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/30/weekly_review_20230430/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-04-19 to 2023-04-30.
In my previous weekly review, I mentioned a journey across multiple cities. After returning to Hangzhou, I gradually resumed my original life rhythm. I had much more time alone, with plenty of input, reflection, and interesting things to do. However, it seems that I had less time to organize and dialogue with myself, often only realizing the passage of time several days later.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #37 - A Fortnight of Leisure (Wuhan | Hong Kong | Mayday)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:39:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from April 3rd to April 18th, 2023.
Perhaps due to my recent change in lifestyle, I had planned numerous engagements as early as March. From the beginning of April, I found myself wandering, experiencing a fortnight of leisure. This journey was akin to a homecoming - departing from Hangzhou where I was raised, to Wuhan, the first place I left home for an extended period, to visit my professor and old friends, and finally to Hong Kong, where I spent some remarkable years, to attend exhibitions and events.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #36 - Gastroenteritis, Nini's Update, and New Journeys</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 12:01:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/04/02/weekly_review_20230402/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-25 to 2023-04-02.
Never did I imagine that as a southerner who lived in Hangzhou for over a decade, I would suffer severe adaptation issues upon returning to live in Hangzhou.
In the previous post, I mentioned that Nini was a bit sick due to the bumpy journey and other factors.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #35 - Newspaper Feature, Moving, and a Sick Nini</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:21:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/24/weekly_review_20230324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-14 to 2023-03-23.
If it weren&amp;rsquo;t for xLog&amp;rsquo;s incentive, I might have skipped this weekly review.
In the past week or so, a series of events unfolded: Nini fell ill, my parents drove to Beijing to pick up the cat (and me), I accompanied them sightseeing (though it was my first time at all the attractions too), met with friends before parting ways, endured a 15-hour cross-city journey, found a new apartment (though it only took an hour to sign the lease), moved and decorated the new place, and started a new job.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #34 - Don't Stop the Clocks</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 17:29:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/13/weekly_review_20230313/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Don&amp;#39;t Stop the Clocks - King Gnu&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-03-08 to 2023-03-13. This week was primarily focused on work handovers, which wasn&amp;rsquo;t as busy as before, but the pressing time and impending tasks still brought considerable pressure. After all, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave a city I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in for nearly two years. More time was spent on conversations and gatherings,</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #33 - Beijing x Story x Farewell</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:30:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-27 to 2023-03-07. This week has brought significant changes to my life, and for various reasons, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave Beijing. With many things to handle, I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating Twitter and my Telegram channel less frequently, and even GitHub has</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #32 - Wuhan, Long-Awaited Reunions, and Flowing Emotions</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:24:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-21 to 2023-02-26. This week was relatively routine in terms of work, with no particularly urgent tasks. Despite being in a somewhat tense state due to personal matters, I felt less anxious and depressed. Perhaps there was a sense that everything</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #31 - Open Source, Front-end Development and ChatGPT Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:51:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/20/weekly_review_20230220/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from February 13, 2023 to February 20, 2023.
This week was exceptionally full with work and various personal projects. Although I wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly busy to the point of having no time to sleep, I developed an inexplicable sense of anxiety and low mood, often leading to a tendency for revenge bedtime procrastination.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #30 - Open Source Budget, Writing Motivation, and Humility Towards Technology</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:41:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/12/weekly_review_20230212/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-07 to 2023-02-12. This week saw little progress in work, yet the time after the New Year seemed to pass particularly quickly. Though it felt like I hadn&amp;rsquo;t accomplished much of value, I found myself in a state of busyness. I</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #29 - Japanese Learning Experience, Steam Deck and Izakaya</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 21:56:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/02/06/weekly_review_20230206/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-01 to 2023-02-06.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first week back at work. Since I had been doing some work during the Spring Festival, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t unaccustomed to the work rhythm. However, I often couldn&amp;rsquo;t freely do my own things, which suddenly made me feel pressed for time.
I started revisiting Japanese and was surprised to find that I still remembered a lot.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #28 - Mastodon, Hometown, and Hide-and-Seek Cat</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/31/weekly_review_20230131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:43:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/31/weekly_review_20230131/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-01-23 to 2023-01-31.
I spent most of this week in my hometown, making up for some regrets, simple yet precious. After returning to Hangzhou, I stayed an extra day to meet friends, then hurried back to Beijing from Hangzhou. Upon arriving home in Beijing, I immediately went to pick up Nini from my colleague&amp;rsquo;s house after barely putting down my luggage.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #27 - What Makes a Home</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:39:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/22/weekly_review_20230122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-01-16 to 2023-01-22.
This week, my time was equally divided between Beijing, Hangzhou, and my hometown in Jiangsu, traveling back and forth. For someone who hasn&amp;rsquo;t left home for almost three months, the journey brought some fatigue, but I found that I&amp;rsquo;m not actually averse to such a long-standing change in my life rhythm, and even feel some novelty and anticipation.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #26 - Blog, Custom Keyboard and New Server</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/15/weekly_review_20230115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:57:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/15/weekly_review_20230115/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from January 10, 2023 to January 15, 2023. The holiday season is approaching, though I don&amp;rsquo;t have much of a sense of ritual for the New Year. Last year, I spent over a week playing through &amp;ldquo;Pokémon Legends: Arceus&amp;rdquo; and revisiting &amp;ldquo;Fire</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #25 - Personal Information Output and Synchronization System Based on Crossbell (Refactored)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:12:56 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from January 1, 2023 to January 9, 2023. This is the first weekly review of 2023. Although the New Year feels like it was just yesterday, the first week of January has already ended. Perhaps my psychological perception of time has become increasingly dull. During the New Year, I wrote a rather detailed annual summary,</description></item><item><title>2022 Year-End Review - Confusion, Low Points and Change</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:18:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Today is the last day of 2022. As I mentioned in my previous weekly review:
There will be an annual summary, covering various events of my year - things lost, things gained, things to be grateful for, and inevitable regrets. Though I hesitated about bringing up certain topics again, I decided to face them truthfully. After all, everything expires, even canned pineapples. This year too shall pass.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #24 - Love Actually</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 20, 2022 to December 27, 2022.
Unconsciously, this is already the 24th article, and the last weekly review of 2022. Sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s this inexplicable sense of ceremony when meaningful events occur at rather round time points, which often makes one particularly happy.
Sometimes the desire to share is just so wondrous.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #23 - How to Learn a New Technology (A Liberal Arts Major's Perspective on Coding)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:20:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/19/weekly_review_20221219/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Brand New Day - Theme song from Flying Colors&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from December 14 to December 19, 2022. This week I continued working from home due to the pandemic (I feel like I can remove this opening line soon, as it has become the norm). I&amp;rsquo;m still &amp;ldquo;slacking off&amp;rdquo; by learning front-end development, while occasionally writing some back-end code for work. On</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #22 - Involution and Anxiety</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 22:24:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/13/weekly_review_20221213/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-12-07 to 2022-12-13.
It&amp;rsquo;s been about 20 cumulative days since I last stepped out of my home. Given the current workload of multiple concurrent projects and the almost-cleared negative status, I haven&amp;rsquo;t planned to return to the office yet. I&amp;rsquo;m even considering staying at home until before the new year. The self-quarantine life is quite pleasant.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #21 - Life Picked Up Again</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/06/weekly_review_20221206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 21:48:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/12/06/weekly_review_20221206/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-11-28 to 2022-12-06.
They say it takes 21 days to form a habit, yet by the 21st weekly review, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t managed to update on schedule. Each week brings a creative excuse for the delay.
The past week wasn&amp;rsquo;t particularly busy work-wise, with features developed for events successfully launched and entering the routine maintenance phase.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #20 - The Loss of Desire to Consume</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:08:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 18 to November 27, 2022.
The weekend has arrived, and for once, I had no concentrated development work. I slept soundly, caught up on some missed episodes in the afternoon, and finally began writing my weekly review. It seems I&amp;rsquo;ve been delaying it for a few days each week, sneakily erasing a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #19 - Remembering a Startup Experience</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 21:25:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/17/weekly_review_20221117/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 9, 2022 to November 17, 2022.
I almost missed this week&amp;rsquo;s review. It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I published on time on Sundays (and it&amp;rsquo;s getting later and later). There are always various things happening. I often comfort myself that it&amp;rsquo;s just a record of my life, and I can lower its priority when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #18 - Companionship and Another Way of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 13:04:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/11/08/weekly_review_20221108/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-11-01 to 2022-11-08.
This week marked the first week of living with my cat. Due to the Double 11 shopping festival, I bought many cat facilities and food. With numerous deliveries arriving, I spent about half of my time working from home and receiving packages, which allowed for more bonding time. The cat is incredibly well-behaved.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #17 - Him and His Cat</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 10:46:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/31/weekly_review_20221031/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 28 to October 31, 2022.
As the previous weekly review was updated quite late, this period seems particularly brief in its time span. However, it holds special significance due to a major change that entered my life.
After a three-day journey to cat shelters from Friday to Sunday, filled with indecision, I brought home a silver point (silver shaded colorpoint?</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #16 - Pure Learning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:28:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/27/weekly_review_20221027/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from October 19 to October 27, 2022.
This week has been busy with work projects, with several consecutive days of overtime, but I&amp;rsquo;ve finally completed my part of the requirements. However, during the spare moments, I managed to go through introductory tutorials for several languages I&amp;rsquo;ve long wanted to learn, which was quite interesting.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #14 - Suspended Life and Self</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:51:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/10/09/weekly_review_20221009/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 27, 2022 to October 9, 2022.
This is a weekly review spanning quite a long period. The reason being that I took leave early on the morning of September 29 and returned to Hangzhou, followed by the National Day holiday, making it a small extended vacation. That week was mainly occupied with overtime work and the journey home, so I decided to merge it into one article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #13 - The Joy of Stealing Time from a Busy Schedule</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 23:19:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/26/weekly_review_20220926/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-19 to 2022-09-26.
This week was unusually busy, with several days where I returned home quite late. Yet, strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s during such times that I seem to find more motivation to do more. I finished a book, caught up on many movies and TV series, and accomplished numerous tasks, both big and small.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #12 - Cyberspace, Self-Definition and Boundaries</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/19/weekly_review_20220919/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/19/weekly_review_20220919/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-09-13 to 2022-09-18.
The past week has been somewhat busy, oscillating between several projects, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much input. I had to work over the weekend but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to stay cooped up at home, so I went out and unexpectedly found a nice café where I spent a pleasant day.
Cyberspace I previously learned about the concept of &amp;ldquo;cyberspace&amp;rdquo; from Reorx&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;Using Automated Workflows to Aggregate Information Intake and Output&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #11 - Moods, Travels and Serendipities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 5, 2022 to September 12, 2022.
The past week was quite enriching, both during the workdays and the Mid-Autumn Festival holiday. Work gradually became busier but also more interesting; daily life saw some changes, no longer so dull and mundane; I&amp;rsquo;ve grown accustomed to pulling out my Kindle for a few pages even during short car rides of just a few dozen minutes, quickly becoming immersed; going out has become more frequent, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just aimlessly walking the streets.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #07 - Learning, Certification and Career Pursuit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 12:36:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/15/weekly_review_20220815/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-08 to 2022-08-15. This week&amp;rsquo;s work still revolved around preparing for an evaluation of the project, mainly focusing on explaining the proposal. Work hours were relatively normal, and I gradually regained a good life rhythm.
However, I felt that after getting used to staying at home after work, I lacked the motivation to go out.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #06 - Sincerity, Games, and Self-Adjustment</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 18:28:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/07/weekly_review_20220807/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-01 to 2022-08-07. In terms of work rhythm, it was far from busy, and I even got home as early as 7 p.m. on several days, which was rare. The extra leisure time allowed me to think more about my personality and state of life, and to organize many previously scattered thoughts.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #05 - Work, Sense of Time Control, and New Friends</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 23:55:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/31/weekly_review_20220731/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 25, 2022, to July 31, 2022, also the first week back to work after a vacation.
After experiencing a rare &amp;ldquo;short summer break,&amp;rdquo; I was immediately thrust into the tense preparation of a new project before I had time to adjust my state, which also prompted me to think more about the balance between work and life.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #04 - Vacation, Family Bonds and Sense of Belonging in Cities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 23:31:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/24/weekly_review_20220724/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here, After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from July 11, 2022 to July 24, 2022. As for the reason for the delay - I was on vacation!!!
Vacation Including my internship, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for over a year now, but because projects have been ongoing, I&amp;rsquo;ve had hardly any complete holidays except for the Spring Festival, and I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated quite a few compensatory days off.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #03 - Health, Goals and the Rhythm of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:30:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface It seems that every time I start with the title, I try to set a theme for the past week. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s not that easy to summarize, but I still persist in doing so. Perhaps this way, life will be like a series of chapters pieced together, and when looking back after a long time, it will feel like a fulfilling book.
This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-07-04 to 2022-07-10.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #02 - Work, Anxiety and Growth</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/03/weekly_review_20220703/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:54:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/07/03/weekly_review_20220703/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface It&amp;rsquo;s been a full year since I started working in Beijing after my internship.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a person with an inexplicable sense of ritual. At this juncture, I frequently reflect on my thoughts, gains, anxieties, and regrets from this past year. I often wonder, on this day a year ago, what would that nervous yet expectant version of myself have hoped to gain from the year ahead?</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #01 - Emotions, Sense of Security, and Living Earnestly</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/28/weekly_review_20220626/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 22:54:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/28/weekly_review_20220626/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface The idea of writing a weekly review had been on my mind since before my birthday. I was initially drawn to the open-source weekly reviews by Xuanwo. On one hand, I aspired to reach a state where I could produce and contribute something every week. On the other hand, I was intrigued by the concept of observing and measuring my life, work, and learning on a weekly scale.</description></item><item><title>Confession at 25: A Love Like a Flower Bouquet</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:01:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/06/yearly_review_25/</guid><description>Preface Today is June 6, 2022, and I am 25 years old. In truth, since that article I wrote two years ago on this day, &amp;ldquo;Confessions at 23: Pursuing Meaning,&amp;rdquo; I had intended to write one every year, as a way to account for the year past, whether it was splendid or mundane. Much indeed happened when I was 23, but each time I opened a blank document, I found</description></item><item><title>Using OKR to Organize My Learning Plan</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/11/learning_plan_okr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/11/learning_plan_okr/</guid><description>Describe in one sentence the ideal state I want to achieve Specific goal scope: Enhance programming technical skills Time period: 2 months Description: I aspire to become a developer with solid programming skills and maintain an open mindset for continuous learning in technology — Objective O Identify keywords, break down the state into goals Areas I need to improve Solid programming skills Open mindset for continuous learning Desired level of achievement Ability to create value through technology Passion and pursuit of technology Continuous learning state like the Bilibili creator &amp;ldquo;Shi Luo Tuo Ya&amp;rdquo; Set indicators for each keyword/goal Solid programming skills: Ability to meet the technical interview requirements of current blockchain companies in Hong Kong/Mainland China, such as Ant Chain, Tencent Blockchain, Hangzhou Qulian Technology, etc.</description></item><item><title>Confessions at 23: Seeking Meaning</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/06/06/yearly_review_23/</guid><description>Confessions of a 23-Year-Old: Seeking Meaning Today is June 6, 2020, and I am 23 years old. This age seems to be an awkward existence. If defined by life stages, my undergraduate graduation is already a year behind, yet it&amp;rsquo;s still too early for two zodiac years. My life experience is far from sufficient to offer advice to others, but I still want to write something to account for my past few years.</description></item></channel></rss>