<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>image-hosting on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/image-hosting/</link><description>Recent content in image-hosting on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:12:47 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/image-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding Privacy and Copyright Protection to Your Image Hosting with WebP Cloud and Cloudflare WAF</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;Building Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)&amp;rdquo;, I constructed a free image hosting system using Cloudflare R2 and optimized images through WebP Cloud.
While using WebP Cloud, I discovered it offered features like custom Proxy User Agent and watermarking. This sparked an idea: could I use WebP Cloud to protect the source links of my image hosting, making WebP Cloud&amp;rsquo;s proxy links the sole entry point for accessing all my images, while also uniformly adding my exclusive copyright watermark?</description></item><item><title>Build Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects, and also started this series of tutorials to document the entire build and deployment process.
This article is about the solution for the image hosting system.
[2024-07-02 Update]
I wrote a new tutorial implementing privacy and copyright protection for the image hosting system, which can be considered an additional chapter.</description></item></channel></rss>