<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vps on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/vps/</link><description>Recent content in vps on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/vps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How I Rescued Critical Data When My Cloud Server Crashed</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/rescue_my_data_from_a_crashed_server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/rescue_my_data_from_a_crashed_server/</guid><description>Preface On Friday, my 2C2G server purchased from BandwagonHost suddenly reported a kernel error, making it impossible to connect via SSH or restart. After a series of circuitous rescue attempts, I finally managed to salvage over a thousand images from my image hosting service. Still shaken by the experience, I&amp;rsquo;d like to document the rescue process and, incidentally, discuss the new image hosting solution I&amp;rsquo;ve set up.
Server Rescue This server had been running stably for about a year and a half, hosting many of my critical services, including over a thousand irreplaceable images for my blog&amp;rsquo;s image hosting service, persistently stored on the host via Docker Volume.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #63 - An Unpleasant Flower Ordering Experience, Merchants and Consumers, and the Increasingly AI-like Humans</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from June 24 to June 30, 2024.
An unpleasant flower ordering and rights protection experience led me to ponder the relationship between merchants and consumers, as well as the phenomenon of humans becoming more AI-like while AI becomes increasingly human-like. On Friday, my server suddenly experienced a Kernel Panic and couldn&amp;rsquo;t reboot. After various roundabout rescue attempts, I finally salvaged over a thousand images from the image bed, leaving me feeling quite shaken.</description></item><item><title>Ghost 5.0 Has Arrived, Let's Deploy It with One Click on Digital Ocean</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_ghost_5_on_digital_ocean_vps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:21:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_ghost_5_on_digital_ocean_vps/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface I am an advocate of static blogs and serverless support. My personal blog and some knowledge base projects are generated using hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages. This approach is convenient for version control and deployment maintenance, but for non-technical individuals, using command-line git operations can be overly complex, and it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly convenient for scenarios involving multiple collaborators.
Last week, a former colleague (non-technical) asked me to help set up a portal website, mainly to showcase company information and publish news, features, tools, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>