<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>career on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/career/</link><description>Recent content in career on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wochenrückblick #58 - Ein Jahr Remote-Arbeit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/04/30/weekly_review_20240430/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Vorwort Dies ist eine Aufzeichnung und Reflexion meines Lebens vom 10. April 2024 bis zum 30. April 2024.
Es ist bereits Mitte April seit meiner Rückkehr aus Bali, und ich begrüße eine weitere große Veränderung in meinem Leben - den erneuten Umzug von Peking nach Hangzhou und die Anmietung einer neuen Wohnung. Der Rhythmus des Lebens hat sich dadurch subtil verändert. Zufälligerweise ist es ein Jahr her, seit ich zuletzt nach Hangzhou zurückgezogen bin, daher möchte ich in diesem Beitrag über mein Jahr der Fernarbeit sprechen.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #20 - The Loss of Desire to Consume</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:08:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/11/27/weekly_review_20221127/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 18 to November 27, 2022.
The weekend has arrived, and for once, I had no concentrated development work. I slept soundly, caught up on some missed episodes in the afternoon, and finally began writing my weekly review. It seems I&amp;rsquo;ve been delaying it for a few days each week, sneakily erasing a week&amp;rsquo;s worth of reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item></channel></rss>