<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mood on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/mood/</link><description>Recent content in mood on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:12:56 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/mood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #25 - Personal Information Output and Synchronization System Based on Crossbell (Refactored)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:12:56 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/01/09/weekly_review_20230109/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from January 1, 2023 to January 9, 2023. This is the first weekly review of 2023. Although the New Year feels like it was just yesterday, the first week of January has already ended. Perhaps my psychological perception of time has become increasingly dull. During the New Year, I wrote a rather detailed annual summary,</description></item><item><title>Jahresrückblick 2022 - Verwirrung, Tiefpunkte und Veränderung</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:18:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/31/yearly_review_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Vorwort Heute ist der letzte Tag des Jahres 2022. Wie ich in meinem letzten Wochenrückblick erwähnte:
Es wird eine Jahresrückschau geben, die verschiedene Ereignisse meines Jahres umfasst - Dinge, die verloren gingen, Dinge, die gewonnen wurden, Dinge, für die ich dankbar bin, und unvermeidliche Bedauern. Obwohl ich zögerte, bestimmte Themen erneut anzusprechen, beschloss ich, ihnen ehrlich zu begegnen. Schließlich läuft alles ab, selbst Ananasdosen. Auch dieses Jahr wird vergehen.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Report #24 - Love Actually</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:59:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/12/27/weekly_review_20221227/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Christmas Song (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 20, 2022 to December 27, 2022.
Unconsciously, this is already the 24th article, and the last weekly report of 2022. Sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s this inexplicable sense of ceremony when meaningful events occur at rather round time points, which often makes one particularly happy.
Sometimes the desire to share is just so wondrous.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #11 - Moods, Travels and Serendipities</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:53:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/09/13/weekly_review_20220913/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from September 5, 2022 to September 12, 2022.
The past week was quite enriching, both during the workdays and the Mid-Autumn Festival holiday. Work gradually became busier but also more interesting; daily life saw some changes, no longer so dull and mundane; I&amp;rsquo;ve grown accustomed to pulling out my Kindle for a few pages even during short car rides of just a few dozen minutes, quickly becoming immersed; going out has become more frequent, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just aimlessly walking the streets.</description></item></channel></rss>