<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>growth on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/growth/</link><description>Recent content in growth on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:42:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Geständnis mit 27: Erwachsenwerden ist eine entmutigende Angelegenheit</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2024/06/06/yearly_review_27/</guid><description>《Reply 1988 OST》 Vorwort Es ist der 6. Juni 2024, und ich bin 27 Jahre alt.
Die Idee für den wöchentlichen Rückblick entstand an meinem Geburtstag vor zwei Jahren. Wie ich in der Zusammenfassung des letzten Jahres erwähnte, ist dies eine Kolumne und ein Ritual, das ich beibehalten möchte, und es ist wie versprochen eingetroffen.
Im ersten Jahr schrieb ich 40 wöchentliche Rückblicke, aber letztes Jahr waren es nur 20.</description></item><item><title>Geständnis mit 26: Der Steinschlepper</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:42:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/06/06/yearly_review_26/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Geständnis mit 26: Der Steinschlepper Es ist der 6. Juni 2023, und ich bin 26 Jahre alt. Mit zunehmendem Alter empfinde ich keine besondere Zeremonie oder Vorfreude mehr für meinen Geburtstag an sich. Dennoch dient er als Meilenstein, der mich daran erinnert, dass ein weiteres Jahr vergangen ist. Seit letztem Jahr habe ich beschlossen, an meinem Geburtstag und zu Silvester einige Worte zu hinterlassen, als eine Art Rechenschaft für die verstrichene Zeit.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #03 - Health, Goals and the Rhythm of Life</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:30:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/11/weekly_review_20220711/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface It seems that every time I start with the title, I try to set a theme for the past week. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s not that easy to summarize, but I still persist in doing so. Perhaps this way, life will be like a series of chapters pieced together, and when looking back after a long time, it will feel like a fulfilling book.
This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-07-04 to 2022-07-10.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #02 - Work, Anxiety and Growth</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/03/weekly_review_20220703/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:54:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/07/03/weekly_review_20220703/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface It&amp;rsquo;s been a full year since I started working in Beijing after my internship.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a person with an inexplicable sense of ritual. At this juncture, I frequently reflect on my thoughts, gains, anxieties, and regrets from this past year. I often wonder, on this day a year ago, what would that nervous yet expectant version of myself have hoped to gain from the year ahead?</description></item></channel></rss>