<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>friend on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/friend/</link><description>Recent content in friend on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/tag/friend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #39 - First COVID Infection, Past Emotions, and Rediscovered Desire to Share</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/05/20/weekly_review_20230520/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from May 1, 2023 to May 20, 2023.
As I type this first line, I realize it has been delayed for three weeks. Many interesting things happened during this period, but it seems my desire to share has been gradually fading. I only jotted down some fragmented thoughts in Logseq, and despite several attempts to organize them, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the right approach.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #37 - A Fortnight of Leisure (Wuhan | Hong Kong | Mayday)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 11:39:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/04/18/weekly_review_20230418/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece chronicles my life and reflections from April 3rd to April 18th, 2023.
Perhaps due to my recent change in lifestyle, I had planned numerous engagements as early as March. From the beginning of April, I found myself wandering, experiencing a fortnight of leisure. This journey was akin to a homecoming - departing from Hangzhou where I was raised, to Wuhan, the first place I left home for an extended period, to visit my professor and old friends, and finally to Hong Kong, where I spent some remarkable years, to attend exhibitions and events.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #33 - Beijing x Story x Farewell</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:30:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/03/07/weekly_review_20230307/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-27 to 2023-03-07. This week has brought significant changes to my life, and for various reasons, I&amp;rsquo;m about to leave Beijing. With many things to handle, I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating Twitter and my Telegram channel less frequently, and even GitHub has</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #32 - Wuhan, Long-Awaited Reunions, and Flowing Emotions</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:24:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2023/02/26/weekly_review_20230226/</guid><description>&amp;#39;クリスマスソング (English Cover) - Matt Cab&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-02-21 to 2023-02-26. This week was relatively routine in terms of work, with no particularly urgent tasks. Despite being in a somewhat tense state due to personal matters, I felt less anxious and depressed. Perhaps there was a sense that everything</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #15 - Introspection and External Seeking</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:38:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/de/2022/10/18/weekly_review_20221018/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from October 10, 2022 to October 18, 2022.
Due to the pandemic, I had been staying at home in Hangzhou. As the weather turned cooler and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought many clothes, I bought a ticket back to Beijing as soon as my health code turned green. I returned to Beijing on Friday. In just half a month, my home had become quite messy, so I spent almost the entire weekend cleaning and organizing.</description></item></channel></rss>