<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:42 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up a Website Analytics System with GoatCounter and Zeabur</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/06/deploy_web_statistics_system_using_goatcounter_and_zeabur/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/08/06/deploy_web_statistics_system_using_goatcounter_and_zeabur/</guid><description>Preface In my article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects. I also started this series of tutorials to document the entire process of setup and deployment.
This article focuses on the analytics system solution.
Analytics System Solution Compared to the blog itself and the commenting system, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t paid much attention to an analytics system for a long time (mainly because there weren&amp;rsquo;t many readers back then).</description></item><item><title>Build Your Free Blog Comment System from Scratch (Remark42 + fly.io)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/22/free_commenting_system_using_remark42_and_flyio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 01:10:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/22/free_commenting_system_using_remark42_and_flyio/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects, and also started this series of tutorials to document the entire process of building and deploying.
This article is about the solution for the commenting system.
Evolution of Commenting Systems I often feel that comments are not just communication between readers and authors, but the content itself is also part of the article.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #64 - Life Is Here (Stoner and Normal People)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/10/weekly_review_20240710/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a reflection on life from July 1st to July 9th, 2024.
This week, I maintained an early rising routine for several days, dedicating time to reading and studying with high efficiency. However, establishing a regular pattern still requires time and adjustment. I&amp;rsquo;m also exploring how to enter and switch work modes more swiftly. I&amp;rsquo;m simultaneously reading several books: &amp;ldquo;Atlas Shrugged&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Normal People&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;What My Bones Know&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Adding Privacy and Copyright Protection to Your Image Hosting with WebP Cloud and Cloudflare WAF</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 06:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/02/protect_your_image_using_webp_and_cloudflare_waf/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;Building Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)&amp;rdquo;, I constructed a free image hosting system using Cloudflare R2 and optimized images through WebP Cloud.
While using WebP Cloud, I discovered it offered features like custom Proxy User Agent and watermarking. This sparked an idea: could I use WebP Cloud to protect the source links of my image hosting, making WebP Cloud&amp;rsquo;s proxy links the sole entry point for accessing all my images, while also uniformly adding my exclusive copyright watermark?</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #63 - An Unpleasant Flower Ordering Experience, Merchants and Consumers, and the Increasingly AI-like Humans</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/07/01/weekly_review_20240701/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Photograph - Ed Sheeran&amp;#39; Preface This piece records and reflects on my life from June 24 to June 30, 2024.
An unpleasant flower ordering and rights protection experience led me to ponder the relationship between merchants and consumers, as well as the phenomenon of humans becoming more AI-like while AI becomes increasingly human-like. On Friday, my server suddenly experienced a Kernel Panic and couldn&amp;rsquo;t reboot. After various roundabout rescue attempts, I finally salvaged over a thousand images from the image bed, leaving me feeling quite shaken.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Free Image Hosting System from Scratch (Cloudflare R2 + WebP Cloud + PicGo)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:12:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/30/free_image_hosting_system_using_r2_webp_cloud_and_picgo/</guid><description>Preface In the article &amp;ldquo;What Changed in My Blog in 2024&amp;rdquo;, I introduced the blog system I built using Serverless platforms and some open-source projects, and also started this series of tutorials to document the entire build and deployment process.
This article is about the solution for the image hosting system.
[2024-07-02 Update]
I wrote a new tutorial implementing privacy and copyright protection for the image hosting system, which can be considered an additional chapter.</description></item><item><title>In 2024, What Changes Have Come to My Blog</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/29/what_changed_in_my_blog_2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/06/29/what_changed_in_my_blog_2024/</guid><description>Preface Two years ago, in the post &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s 2022, Let&amp;rsquo;s Talk About Why I&amp;rsquo;m Still Blogging&amp;rdquo;, I discussed the origins, intentions, and setup of my blog.
More than two years have passed. The original intention remains, and the writing has persevered, though I haven&amp;rsquo;t achieved the weekly updates I planned. Nevertheless, I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated a fair amount of written work.
Having experienced much, I seem to have gradually transformed into a &amp;ldquo;weekly review blogger,&amp;rdquo; with content and style that have greatly changed.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #56 - Meeting Randy and Taking the Driver's Test</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/31/weekly_review_20240331/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/31/weekly_review_20240331/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from March 25, 2024 to March 31, 2024.
The happiest event this week was meeting Randy. My fan dream came true, and we had a delightful conversation. To avoid impacting work, I woke up at 5 AM for four or five consecutive days to practice driving at the school. It was tough, but I passed the second stage of the driver&amp;rsquo;s test in one go - worth it.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #55 - Oil Painting Experience, Blog System Upgrade, and Thoughts on Self-Hosting</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/24/weekly_review_20240324/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:20:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/03/24/weekly_review_20240324/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Fix You - Coldplay&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2024-03-17 to 2024-03-24.
This week, I rekindled much of my enthusiasm for work and learning, completing the long-listed blog comment system and data statistics system migration in my TODO list, giving me a sense of tidying up my desk. Over the weekend, I experienced oil painting for the first time, painting a new avatar for myself, filled with a sense of accomplishment.</description></item><item><title>Why I'm Still Blogging in 2022</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/12/why_i_still_write_blog_in_2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/06/12/why_i_still_write_blog_in_2022/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Recently, I published several articles introducing my blog setup process and components. Many friends followed my tutorial and set up their own blogs. Meanwhile, some friends raised questions: In 2022, with so many mature writing and publishing platforms available, why do we still go to such lengths to set up and update our own blogs?
I started writing on WeChat Official Account in my freshman year (2015), sharing articles about books, movies, and personal life.</description></item><item><title>Hugo + GitHub Action: Building Your Automated Blog Publishing System</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:39:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_your_blog_using_hugo_and_github_action/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface In a previous article, &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis)&amp;rdquo;, I mentioned using Hugo, a static site generator, to truly build my personal blog. I made some personal customizations and configurations based on the hugo-theme-den theme from the Hugo open-source community to meet my needs.
My solution primarily consists of the following core components:
Personal blog source repository for version control of blog configurations and all article .</description></item><item><title>Ghost 5.0 Has Arrived, Let's Deploy It with One Click on Digital Ocean</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_ghost_5_on_digital_ocean_vps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:21:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/29/deploy_ghost_5_on_digital_ocean_vps/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface I am an advocate of static blogs and serverless support. My personal blog and some knowledge base projects are generated using hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages. This approach is convenient for version control and deployment maintenance, but for non-technical individuals, using command-line git operations can be overly complex, and it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly convenient for scenarios involving multiple collaborators.
Last week, a former colleague (non-technical) asked me to help set up a portal website, mainly to showcase company information and publish news, features, tools, etc.</description></item><item><title>Lightweight Open Source Free Blog Comment System Solution (Cusdis + Railway)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/24/free_and_lightweight_blog_comment_system_using_cusdis_and_railway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:47:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/24/free_and_lightweight_blog_comment_system_using_cusdis_and_railway/</guid><description>《Here, After Us - Mayday》 Preface Previously, I wrote an article titled &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis),&amp;rdquo; detailing my blog system built using Serverless and some open-source projects. I also started a series to document the setup process.
This article focuses on the blog comment system solution. The earliest comment system I used was the notorious Disqus, a cumbersome system known for collecting user privacy data.</description></item><item><title>Building a Free Personal Blog Analytics System from Scratch (umami + Vercel + Heroku)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/21/free_blog_analysis_using_umami_vercel_and_heroku/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:56:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/05/21/free_blog_analysis_using_umami_vercel_and_heroku/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface Previously, I wrote an article titled &amp;ldquo;Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + GitHub Pages + Cusdis)&amp;rdquo;, detailing my blog system built using Serverless and some open-source projects. I also started a series to document the setup process.
A few days ago, I came across an article by Reorx titled &amp;ldquo;Deploy umami for Personal Website Analytics&amp;rdquo;. He introduced the umami project and demonstrated its serverless deployment using Railway.</description></item><item><title>Free Personal Blog System Setup and Deployment Solution (Hugo + Cloudflare Pages + Cusdis)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 01:19:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/03/24/free_blog_deploy_using_hugo_and_cusdis/</guid><description>Preface Pseudoyu is my personal blog website. Initially built using WordPress on my Vultr VPS, it was later migrated to a Tencent Cloud server and registered for improved access speed. However, the publishing process remained cumbersome, and server maintenance incurred significant long-term expenses.
Thus, I continuously explored solutions that could ensure optimal access experience both domestically and internationally while being hosted on platforms that streamline deployment and publishing processes. I&amp;rsquo;ve been constantly refining my blog system setup and publishing workflow.</description></item></channel></rss>