<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>e-commerce on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/e-commerce/</link><description>Recent content in e-commerce on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 09:19:19 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Look at Tik-Tok</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/16/ecom6013_discussion_topic4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 09:19:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/16/ecom6013_discussion_topic4/</guid><description>A Look at Tik-Tok Given there are many social media platforms already existing in US, what makes Tik-Tok so successful that it becomes a big enough threat to cause the US Government to act the way it did towards a commercial company (ignore political factors) Economically, at about 2016, US tech giants such as Facebook or Google mainly focused on long video platform instead of the short video platform. A company called Musical.</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 8 Blockchain and Cybercurrency</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/09/ecom6013_topic8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 11:01:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/09/ecom6013_topic8/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 8 Blockchain and Cybercurrency Form of Money
Token money Physical token Value is lost without the token No intermediary is required for spending Requires faith in the issuer (a government or a bank) Notationary money Notation/entry in a ledger, passbook, or database Can&amp;rsquo;t be lost Requires an intermediary Requires faith in the maintainer of the ledger Hybrid money Requires both a token and a ledger account Can be lost Requires an intermediary Requires faith in the issuer Virtual money No token/ledger Can be lost No intermediary required No issuer, no government backing Digital money String of bytes (data) stored on a device Value is lost/stolen when devices fail/invaded Cybercurrency Bitcoin is the most influential one Based on blockchain Bitcoin</description></item><item><title>Mobile Payment Systems Case Study</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/01/ecom6013_discussion_topic3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 22:25:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/01/ecom6013_discussion_topic3/</guid><description>Mobile Payment Systems Why has China been an ideal environment to support mobile payment systems Politically, payment licenses are controlled by government (relative financial institutions) and under strict regulation. So, tech giants like Alibaba who are qualified can increasingly develop their payment business in the early age. Plus, in the early stage of mobile payment, laws and rules are not so completed. Payment platform can utilize smart market strategies (like very high return rate) to attract more new potential users and enhance existing users’ engagement, which is effective in market expanding stage.</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 7 E-Payment Systems</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/27/ecom6013_topic7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 11:30:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/27/ecom6013_topic7/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 7 E-Payment Systems Payment System Stakeholders&amp;rsquo; Priorities
Customer Low-risk Low-cost Refutable Convenience Reliable Merchants Low-risks Low-cost Irrefutable Secure Reliable Financial intermediaries Secure Low-risk Maximizing profit Government regulators Secure Trust Protecting participants and enforcing reporting Type of Payment Systems
Cash Cheque transfer Credit card Stored value Accumulating balance B2C Payment System
Credit cards Financial cybermediaries Electronic bill presentment and payment Smart cards Mobile payment Features
Make large purchases Will not pay with credit card or financial cybermediary Use financial EDI (Electronic Data Interchange) Pay for many purchases at once Likely that cloud-based payment gateway (or other Internet-based technology) will eventually take over completely!</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 6 E-Commerce Security</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/26/ecom6013_topic6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 15:46:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/26/ecom6013_topic6/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 6 E-Commerce Security Good E-Commerce Security
Highest degree of security New technologies Organizational policies and procedures Industry standards and government law Other factors Cost of security vs. potential loss Security often breaks at weakest link The Tense Between Security and Other Values
Security vs. Easy of use More Secure -&amp;gt; More difficult to use + slower Security vs. Desire of individuals to act anonmously Basic E-Commerce Security Issues and Landscape</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 5 Mobile Commerce</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/21/ecom6013_topic5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 10:44:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/21/ecom6013_topic5/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 5 Mobile Commerce Basic Principle of Mobile Technology
FDMA (Frequency Division Multiple Access) TDMA (Time Division Multiple Access) CDMA (Code Division Multiple Access) Fundamental Mobility: Cellphones
Cell Handover
4G vs. 5G
4G 10 ms 100 Thousand Connections / km^2 1 Gbps 5G &amp;lt; 1ms 1 Million Connections / km^2 20 Gbps E-Commerce vs. M-Commerce
E-Commerce Device: PC Network: Internet (HTTP) M-Commerce Device: Mobile devices Network Mobile carrier network WiFi Local frequency (RFID/NFC) Definition of M-Commerce</description></item><item><title>New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc.</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/18/ecom6013_discussion_topic2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 01:25:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/18/ecom6013_discussion_topic2/</guid><description>E-Commerce Presence Look Around New iPad Air 4 (2020) Presence by Apple Inc Website Link
The iPad Air 4 (2020) got shown off at Apple&amp;rsquo;s September event held on September 16. There is a specific designed website (mobile version included) for this product. I&amp;rsquo;d like to do an analysis towards this very impressive E-Commerce presence.
Apple iPad Air product line is mainly targeted to educators/students, staffs and kids/teenagers. So, the most premium features this new product wants to convey to customers is its fancy appearance and powerful A14 Bionic for creation, study and entertainment.</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 4 Website Design, Testing and Maintenance</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 21:25:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic4/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 4 Website Design, Testing and Maintenance Planing: The Systems Development Life Cycle
Systems analysis/planing Busisess objectives System functionalities Information requirements Systems design Building the system Testing Implementation Quality Consideration
Navigation Accessibility Scalability Reliability Maintainability Usability Compatibility and interoperability Security Readability In-House / Outsourcing (Hiring vendors to provide services)
Build own / outsourcing Host own / outsourcing (preferred) Implementation, Maintenance, and Optimization
Systems break down unpredictably
Ongoing maintenance Benchmarking Website Optimization</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 3 E-Commerce Presence</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 20:25:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic3/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 3 E-Commerce Presence Image You E-Commerce Presence
Idea Mission Target audience Intended market space Strategic analysis Marketing matrix Development timeline Preliminary budget About Money (e.g. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce &amp;amp; Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS) Business models Revenue models About target audience Demographics Lifestyle Consumption patterns &amp;hellip; Marketplace Characteristics Size Growth Demographics Structure Content SWOT Analysis E-Commerce presence map Milestones Costs Simple website: US$5000 Small startup: US$25,000 tp US$50,000 Large corporate website: US$100,000 + to millions SWOT Analysis</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 2 Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 19:28:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/ecom6013_topic2/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 2 Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture Internet
Interconnected network of thousands of networks and hundreds of millions of computers Links businesses, educational institutions, government agencies, and individuals World Wide Web (WWW)
One of the internet&amp;rsquo;s most popular services Provides access to billions, possibly trillions, of Web pages Evolution of Internet
Innovation phase (1961 - 1974) Institutionalization phase (1975 - 1995) Commercialization Phase (1995 - present) Packet Switching</description></item><item><title>Puma Goes Omni Case Study</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/08/ecom6013_discussion_topic1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 23:30:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/08/ecom6013_discussion_topic1/</guid><description>Puma Goes Omni About Puma Puma Official Website
A Fancy Presentation
Slogan: &amp;ldquo;Run The Streets. Do You.&amp;rdquo;
The third largest sportswear manufacture in the world. (2018)
The company was founded in 1948 by Rudolf Dassler.
Building a Centralize Website Restructuring Strategy
Replacing multiple e-commerce sites on different platform Unifying content and product strategies Building multiple teams in different regions, separate tasks Content Management System (CMS)
&amp;ldquo;Database software program specifically designed to manage structures, unstructured data and objects in a Website environment.</description></item><item><title>ECOM6013 Topic 1 Introduction to E-Commerce Technology</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/06/ecom6013_topic1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 04:28:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/06/ecom6013_topic1/</guid><description>ECOM6013 E-Commerce Technologies Topic 1 Introduction to E-Commerce Technology Discussion Topic #1: Puma Goes Omni
What is the purpose of Puma&amp;rsquo;s content management systems? Why did Puma build a single centralized website rather than continue with multiple websites serving different countries and regions? [choosen] What social media sites does Puma use, and what do they contribute to Puma&amp;rsquo;s marketing effort? Case Study
Alibaba Singles&amp;rsquo; Day 2019
Core E-Commerce Technologies Introduction to E-Commerce Technology Internet and E-Commerce Infrasture E-Commerce Presence and Development Life Circle Web Design, Implementation and Testing Introduction to Mobile Commerce Internet and E-Commerce Commerce Electronic Payment Systems Cybercurrency, Bitcoin and Blockchain Emerging Technology &amp;amp; Cloud Computing and IoT Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning and E-Commerce Trends E-Commerce and Data Science</description></item></channel></rss>