<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>machine learning on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/machine-learning/</link><description>Recent content in machine learning on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 16:30:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>xDeepFM for Recommender Systems</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/11/11/comp7404_group_project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 16:30:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/11/11/comp7404_group_project/</guid><description>Preface eXtreme Deep Factorization Machine (xDeepFM)
This paper proposes a novel Compressed Interaction Network (CIN), which aims to generate feature interactions in an explicit fashion and at the vector-wise level.
Github Repository GitHub: xDeepFM_for_Recommender_Systems
Video Demo YouTube | Google Drive
Datasets Criteo Dataset. It is a famous industry benchmarking dataset for developing models predicting ad click-through rate, and is publicly accessible. Given a user and the page he is visiting, the goal is to predict the probability that he will clik on a given ad Running Environment I strongly recommmend that you use Anaconda to implement this project.</description></item><item><title>COMP7404 Topic 3 Adversarial Search</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/05/comp7404_topic3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:30:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/05/comp7404_topic3/</guid><description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 3 Adversarial Search A Multi-agent Competitive Environment
Other agents are planning against us Goals are in conflict (not necessarily) Game Definition
A game can be defined as s : States s0: Initial state Player(s) : Defines which player has the move Actions(s) : Returns a set of legal moves Result(s,a) : Defines the result of a move TerminalTest(s) : True when game is over, false otherwise Utility(s,p) : Defines the final numeric value for a game that ends in terminal state s for player p A game tree can be constructed Nodes are game states and edges are moves Tic-Tac-Toe Game Tree</description></item><item><title>COMP7404 Topic 2 Beyond Classical Search</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/04/comp7404_topic2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 21:30:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/10/04/comp7404_topic2/</guid><description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 2 Beyond Classical Search Planning vs Identification
Planing: sequence of actions The path to the goal is the important thing Paths have various costs, depths Heuristics to guide, frontier to keep backups Identification: assignments to variables The goal itself is important, not the path Local Search can find solutions faster for specific types of identification problems
Local Search
Evaluate and modify one current state rather than systematically explore paths from an initial state Suitable for problems were all that matters in the solution state and not the path cost to reach it Although local search algorithms are not systematic they have two advantages Require very little memory Often find reasonable solutions in large spaces Local Search Algorithm</description></item><item><title>COMP7404 Topic 1 Solving Problems by Searching</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404_topic1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:28:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2020/09/16/comp7404_topic1/</guid><description>COMP7404 Computational Intelligence and Machine Learning Topic 1 Solving Problems by Searching Types of Search
Uninformed Search (Know nothing about the problem except definition) Informed Search (know something more like how close to the goal) Local Search (Randomly initilize a state and make it better, e.g. Deep Learning) Constraint Satisfaction Problems (Know more about the problem) Adversarial Search (have an opponent, e.g. chess, star craft game) Is Search the same as Unsupervised/Supervised Learning?</description></item></channel></rss>