<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>storage on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/storage/</link><description>Recent content in storage on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 09:30:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/storage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blockchain Network Storage and Optimization Based on CNFS</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/08/20/blockchain_paper_cnfs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 09:30:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/08/20/blockchain_paper_cnfs/</guid><description>Research on Cloud Computing Processing and Optimization of Distributed Computer Preface After a year of blockchain-related studies at HKU, I developed an interest in the field of distributed storage. My graduation project was also related to IPFS, as detailed in &amp;ldquo;Uright - Blockchain Music Copyright Management ÐApp&amp;rdquo;. Upon returning to the mainland, I had the opportunity to collaborate with Dr. Sun Ye from CNFS Protocol Lab to write this paper, &amp;ldquo;Research on Cloud Computing Processing and Optimization of Distributed Computer (Blockchain Network Storage and Optimization Based on CNFS)&amp;rdquo;, which deepened my understanding of distributed network storage and computing.</description></item><item><title>Setting Up an IPFS Local Node (Command Line)</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/27/blockchain_ipfs_practice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 18:46:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/27/blockchain_ipfs_practice/</guid><description>Preface In the previous article, &amp;ldquo;IPFS Distributed File Storage Principles&amp;rdquo;, we provided a detailed introduction to the design concepts, functions, working principles, and IPNS of the IPFS system. So, how do we set up an IPFS node locally?
This article demonstrates the setup of an IPFS node (command-line version) on the macOS 11.2.3 system, and performs actual operations on file uploading, downloading, network synchronization, pin, GC, IPNS, etc., to deepen the understanding of IPFS working principles.</description></item><item><title>Analysis and Reflections on IPFS Distributed Storage Protocol</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/25/blockchain_ipfs_structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 16:30:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/25/blockchain_ipfs_structure/</guid><description>Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a school Case Study project, which is a music copyright management project based on the Ethereum platform. It uses IPFS distributed file storage technology for uploading music works and copyright proof documents, mainly utilizing its deduplication feature to detect infringement. I became interested in the IPFS system and read the IPFS series articles on the QTech platform. I also consulted some related materials and</description></item></channel></rss>