<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reading on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/reading/</link><description>Recent content in reading on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 19:13:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Review #53 - Three Blank Months, Life Adrift, and Spring Festival</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 19:13:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2024/02/29/weekly_review_20240229/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from December 4, 2023, to February 29, 2024. Much has transpired over the past few months, across various dimensions of life, making it challenging to begin writing this weekly review, which was originally intended to document daily life and personal thoughts. It seemed that no single or even two issues could summarize everything, and</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #52 - Self-effacing Personality and Another Perspective on Love</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 22:15:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/12/03/weekly_review_20231203/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Special Person - Khalil Fong&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from November 30, 2023 to December 3, 2023.
On Sunday evening, while organizing various files, I realized upon opening the document that many previous issues were written in the crevices of workdays. Coincidentally, I returned to Hangzhou on Friday night, having more time to myself. I thought about not delaying the weekly review until midweek to avoid rushing.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #51 - Admiring Lawrence and Falling Ill</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/29/weekly_review_20231129/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2023-11-22 to 2023-11-29.
This week, my senior and I were both confined at home recovering from influenza A, which significantly impacted our work and daily life. I finished recording the podcast I mentioned last time, chatting casually for over an hour. Despite running a fever for two days over the weekend, I struggled to go out on Sunday to attend Lawrence&amp;rsquo;s offline event.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #50 - A Stroll in the Temple of Heaven, Rediscovering Reading, and the Feynman Technique</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:41:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2023/11/21/weekly_review_20231122/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Tenderness - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from November 13 to November 21, 2023.
This week had quite a bit of discussion and development at work, maintaining a normal rhythm. My days were largely occupied by work, study, and additional reading, giving me a sense of fulfillment. As I plan to spend more evenings reading books, I hurried to finish the few dramas and anime I was watching.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #10 - Returning to the Past, Regrets and the Present</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 23:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/04/weekly_review_20220904/</guid><description>《Here After Us - Mayday》 Preface This piece is a record and reflection of my life from 2022-08-29 to 2022-09-04.
I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated many unedited original photos from the past. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly organizing them now. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m selecting a work that fits the theme as much as possible for each cover image. I&amp;rsquo;ll see if I can select some as specific themed portfolios later.
I&amp;rsquo;m quite surprised to hear from several friends in real life that they&amp;rsquo;re following my weekly reviews.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #09 - Colorless Yu and His Year of Pilgrimage</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 11:08:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/29/weekly_review_20220829/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record and reflection of my life from August 22, 2022 to August 28, 2022.
This week, there were finally some changes at work. I entered another project that I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in and more challenging. I feel I can put to use some of the contract and underlying chain-related knowledge I learned while working from home. A colleague I was quite close to left the company mid-week.</description></item><item><title>Weekly Review #08 - Career Musings, 404 Not Found, and Cats</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:22:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/08/22/weekly_review_20220822/</guid><description>&amp;#39;Here After Us - Mayday&amp;#39; Preface This is a record of and reflection on my life from August 16 to August 21, 2022. Work remained relatively relaxed this week, allowing for more time to converse and dine with colleagues midweek. With limited time at home, the overall pace was leisurely. The atmosphere of July and August felt reminiscent of summer vacations past, unburdened by any sense of guilt. Nevertheless, I managed to read some books and establish a more regular reading routine in terms of time, frequency, and approach.</description></item></channel></rss>