<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>database on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/database/</link><description>Recent content in database on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 23:30:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/database/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PostgreSQL Basics and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 23:30:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2022/09/05/database_postgres_basic/</guid><description>《后来的我们 - 五月天》 Preface Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about organizing and summarizing the technical points and tools commonly used in my work. On one hand, this helps me review these knowledge points and deepen my memory of their usage. On the other hand, it can serve as a reference for future use. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m planning to cover several core areas including databases,</description></item><item><title>MySQL Fundamentals and Practice</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:12:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/29/database_mysql_basic/</guid><description>Preface Databases are commonly used in both foundational learning and real enterprise business scenarios. There&amp;rsquo;s often a jest that daily work always revolves around CRUD operations. Proficiency in using mainstream relational databases is a fundamental skill for developers. This article will provide an overview of the basic knowledge and related operations of MySQL, a popular relational database, on the MacOS system for easy reference.
Overview of Data and Databases Data Fundamentally, data is a type of fact or observed result, a logical summary of objective matters, and a form and carrier of information.</description></item><item><title>COMP7801 Topic 4 Top-k</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/06/comp7801_topic4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/06/comp7801_topic4/</guid><description>Background Multidimensional Data Flat relational tables Multimedia feature vectors Data warehouse data Spatial data Text documents Attribute Types Attributes of multidimensional tuples may have variable types Ordinal (e.g., age, salary) Nominal categorical values (e.g., color, religion) Binary (e.g., gender, owns_property)Basic queries: range, NN, similarity Basic Queries (Range) selection query Returns the records that qualify a (multidimensional) range predicate Example: Return the employees of age between 45 and 50 and salary above $100,000 Distance (similarity) query Returns the records that are within a distance from a reference record.</description></item><item><title>COMP7801 Topic 3 Spatial Networks</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/27/comp7801_topic3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/27/comp7801_topic3/</guid><description>Background Network Distance In many real applications accessibility of objects is restricted by a spatial network Examples Driver looking for nearest gas station Mobile user looking for nearest restaurant Shortest path distance used instead of Euclidean distance SP(a,b) = path between a and b with the minimum accumulated length Challenges Euclidean distance is no longer relevant R-tree may not be useful, when search is based on shortest path distance Graph cannot be flattened to a one-dimensional space Special storage and indexing techniques for graphs are required Graph properties may vary directed vs.</description></item><item><title>COMP7801 Topic 2 Spatial Data Management</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/06/comp7801_topic2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/02/06/comp7801_topic2/</guid><description>Spatial Data Management Concepts Spatial Data
Location data Check-in service Online Maps Location-based services Location tracking Traffic Data Spatial Databases
PostgreSQL with PostGIS Neo4J-spatial HadoopGIS Ingres GeoMesa Spatial Data Management
Spatial Database Systems Manage large collections of multidimensional objects (2D/3D) A spatial object Contains (at least) one spatial attributes that describes its location and/or geometry A spatial relation Is an organized collection of spatial objects of the same entity Spatial Data Representation</description></item><item><title>COMP7801 Topic 1b Database Indexing</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/01/30/comp7801_topic1b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/01/30/comp7801_topic1b/</guid><description>Database Indexing Concepts Indexing mechanisms used to speed up access to desired data Search Key An attribute or a set of attributes used to look up records in a file An index file consists of records (called index entries) of the form search key - pointer Index files are typically much smaller than the original file Two basic kinds of indices Ordered indices: search keys are stored in sorted order Hash indices: search keys are distributed across &amp;ldquo;buckets&amp;rdquo; using a &amp;ldquo;hash function&amp;rdquo; Good Index Index quality is evaluated by several factors Access types supported by the index efficiently records with a specified value in the attribute (equality query) or records with an attribute value falling in a specified range of values (range query) Access time – query response time Insertion time – data record insertion time Deletion time – data record deletion time Space overhead – size of the index file Classification of Indexes Primary index In a sequentially ordered file, the index whose search key specifies the sequential order of the file Secondary index an index whose search key specifies an order different from the sequential order of the file Also called non-clustered index Dense index Index record appears for every search-key value in the file Sparse Index Contains index records for only some search-key values Applicable when records are sequentially ordered on search-key Less space and less maintenance overhead for insertions and deletions Generally slower than dense index for locating records Good tradeoff: sparse index with an index entry for every block in file, corresponding to least search-key value in the block Primary and Secondary Indices Secondary indices have to be dense Indices offer substantial benefits when searching for records Index is much smaller than relation file (cheap scan) Index can be ordered (fast search) When a file is modified, every index on the file must be updated Updating indices imposes overhead on database modification Indexes should be used with care Sequential scan using primary index is efficient, but a sequential scan using a secondary index is expensive Each record access may fetch a new block from disk Multilevel Index If index does not fit in memory, access becomes expensive To reduce number of disk accesses to index records, treat 1st level of index kept on disk as a sequential file and construct a sparse index on it outer index – a sparse index on 1st-level index file inner index – the 1st-level index file If even outer index is too large to fit in main memory, yet another level of index can be created, and so on B+-Tree Index Files A dynamic, multi-level index Advantage automatically reorganizes itself with small local changes, in the face of insertions and deletions Reorganization of entire file is not required to maintain performance Disadvantage of B+-trees Extra insertion and deletion overhead, space overhead Advantages of B+-trees outweigh disadvantages, and they are used extensively Basic Properties Disk-based tree structure every node of the tree is a block and has an address (block-id) on the disk Multiway tree each node has multiple children (between n/2 and n, where n/2 is the order or degree of the tree) Therefore, at least 50% of the space in a node is guaranteed to be occupied (this rule may not apply to tree root) Balanced tree all paths from the root to a leaf have the same length guarantees good search performance (to be seen later) Disjoint partition of attribute domain into ranges each sub-tree indexes a range in the attribute domain the entries of a directory node define the separators between domain intervals leaf nodes store index entries and pointers to the relation file Non-Leaf Nodes in B+-Trees Each non-leaf node contains up to n-1 search key values and up to n pointers All non-leaf nodes (except root) contain at least n/2 pointers (n/2 is sometimes called the minimum fan-out or degree) Non leaf nodes form a multi-level sparse index on the leaf nodes.</description></item><item><title>COMP7801 Topic 1a Relational Database</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/01/23/comp7801_topic1a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 01:18:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/01/23/comp7801_topic1a/</guid><description>Relational Databases Structure of Relational Databases Basic structure Given sets D1, D2, &amp;hellip;, Dn A relation r is a subset of D1 x D2 x &amp;hellip;, x Dn A relation is a set of n-tuples (a1, a2, &amp;hellip;, an) where each ai Di Example
if customer-name = {Jones, Smith, Curry, Lindsay} customer-street = {Main, North, Park} customer-city = {Harrison, Rye, Pittsfield} Then r = {(Jones, Main, Harrison), (Smith, North, Rye), (Curry, North, Rye), (Lindsay, Park, Pittsfield)} is a relation over customer-name x customer-street x customer-city Attribute Types Each attribute of a relation has a name The set of allowed values for each attribute is called the domain of the attribute Relation Schema A1, A2, &amp;hellip;, An are attributes R = (A1, A2, &amp;hellip;, An ) is a relation schema E.</description></item></channel></rss>