<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hyperledger fabric on Pseudoyu</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/hyperledger-fabric/</link><description>Recent content in hyperledger fabric on Pseudoyu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:52 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/tag/hyperledger-fabric/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction and Architecture of Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) Platforms</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/07/blockchain_baas_platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/07/blockchain_baas_platform/</guid><description>Preface In my current work, I am responsible for the chaincode management portion of a Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) platform for Hyperledger Fabric. I&amp;rsquo;m quite interested in the architecture and implementation of BaaS platforms. As a platform that provides developers with one-stop creation, management, and maintenance of blockchain applications, what does its architecture look like?
This article is a summary and analysis of the BaaS platform architecture.
Introduction to BaaS Blockchain is a complex distributed system, especially enterprise consortium chain platforms like Hyperledger Fabric, where deployment and operation are extremely intricate.</description></item><item><title>Hyperledger Fabric Go SDK Event Analysis</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/01/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_gosdk_event/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:21:58 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/09/01/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_gosdk_event/</guid><description>Preface Recently, while working on a cross-chain adapter, I needed to use the Go SDK to connect to a Fabric network on a local chain and listen for events. Therefore, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to summarize the events supported by Fabric and the listening methods provided by the SDK.
Fabric Events Events are a way for clients to interact with the Fabric network. As shown in the image above, after executing a transaction in the Fabric network, because it is done asynchronously, the client cannot obtain the submitted transaction status (whether it was accepted).</description></item><item><title>A Brief Analysis of Hyperledger Fabric Network and Security System</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/23/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 12:12:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/23/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_network/</guid><description>Preface In the previous article, &amp;ldquo;Detailed Explanation of Hyperledger Fabric Architecture&amp;rdquo;, we provided a comprehensive interpretation and analysis of Fabric&amp;rsquo;s architecture and operational principles. As an enterprise-grade blockchain system, how does it construct networks based on complex business requirements? What security issues exist during its operation, and how does Fabric preventively address these issues through its mechanisms?
This article will illustrate how a simplified enterprise Fabric network is constructed through examples, and analyze its network and security system.</description></item><item><title>Detailed Explanation of Hyperledger Fabric System Architecture</title><link>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/20/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_structure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 12:12:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.pseudoyu.com/en/2021/03/20/blockchain_hyperledger_fabric_structure/</guid><description>Preface As my graduation case study project was primarily based on the Ethereum public chain and lacked enterprise application scenarios, my previous understanding of Hyperledger Fabric was mostly limited to concepts such as its permission management mechanism, channels, and flexible smart contract writing. I had only a vague understanding of its architecture, the roles of various nodes, and operational mechanisms. Recently, while taking the course &amp;ldquo;FITE3011 Distributed Ledger and Blockchain&amp;rdquo; at HKU, the professor provided a detailed explanation of Hyperledger Fabric&amp;rsquo;s working principles, network setup, and chaincode-related knowledge.</description></item></channel></rss>